<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_hello_no_vodka_0">
		<text>Fuck, I can't work like  this; I need a drink bad. Hey, Listen man, Can you bring me a bottle and I will give you some useful info. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_hello_no_vodka_1">
		<text>Here you go, you drunkard.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_hello_no_vodka_111">
		<text>text in default</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_hello_no_vodka_2">
		<text>Fine, I'll bring you some when I get the chance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_hello_no_vodka_222">
		<text>text in default</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_0">
		<text>What do you have to offer?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_1">
		<text>Yeahhh.. man, I'll uhh... How you say it.. Formulate! yeah.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_2">
		<text>...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_3">
		<text>Anyway, here’s the deal.  Really, I can make a BTR out of a tin can if I had the blueprints. So yeah, I found out there are blueprints out there for a special suit called a thermosuit and its right up my alley. Way back, I could make one from scratch but alas I lost the design plans. Anyway, the blueprints should be separated to 3 parts and one of them is in the hands of our dealer, Olivius. I'd go to him myself but I am so hangover that my hands and legs are shaking. Could you go there and get it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_4">
		<text>Sure, I'll do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_44">
		<text>Bro, do it yourself, I can't be assed to go there right now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_zub_0">
		<text>Olivius, Real talk time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_zub_1">
		<text>I'm listening.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_zub_2">
		<text> Limpid Told me that you have a flashdrive with blueprints for a high-tier badass suit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_zub_3">
		<text>Yeah, it's true. Only, I am not going to give it away for free. Tell him that, if he wants that the flashdrive he needs to pay me what he owes me first. 
</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_quest_1_zub_4">
		<text>text in default</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_0">
		<text>I'm back from X-18, any news?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_1">
		<text>Alive you devil! How’s doublet?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_11">
		<text>Alive you devil!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_12">
		<text> Alive and healthy as ever and I've managed to find some info. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_13">
		<text>Alright then, What are you waiting for? Tell me what you managed to find out.
</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_14">
		<text>I have Literally dug through everything there. I've found many interesting places. One of them scared the living hell out of me. In it, there were a few ritual fires lit and in those fires heads and corpses of stalkers were burning on stakes. The whole room looked like death. In this room I found a part of the documents but when I picked them up I was ambushed by a controller. Although, I doubt this lair was his.
</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_15">
		<text> In that case, duty's hypothesis that Sin had a lair inside the laboratory is most likely correct but I have no idea why they would abandon it. Anyway, have you found the second part? 
</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_16">
		<text>Yes, I had no problem getting the second part. Here you go. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_17">
		<text>I need some time sort these out and as for you, a good job should always be paid well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_2">
		<text>Alive and healthy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_22">
		<text>We begun the operation as planned but, alas, he didn't make it. May he rest in peace. I had to finish the job alone. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_final_222">
		<text>In the last minute he decided to renege on our contract and hence I had to do the job alone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_0">
		<text>Hey, What's up. I heard you need help. Sidorovich should have said I'd be here.
</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_1">
		<text>Uh-huh, you must be the "trustworthy person" that sidrovich sent. Only one problem, you're late. I already gave the job to someone else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_11">
		<text> Yeah, and You must be the "trustworthy person" Sidrovich talked about. He told me you'd come here. He said you are a reliable guy and I am putting a lot of fate in you. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_2">
		<text> So, Isn't there anything we can do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_22">
		<text>Great. What needs to be done?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_3">
		<text>No, You're just in time. The mission isn't easy and the stalker who takes the job will need backup. 
</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_33">
		<text>The documents, that you stole from the military, mention a few secert places. Even though they are highly encrypted, I did manage to find the location of one of the secret facilities. It is a lab by the name of x-18 located in Dark-Valley. Everything adds up, a secret laboratory was found in those parts. It's mentioned in the docs that a lot of the radioactive rubbish in Garbage came from x18.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_4">
		<text>Alright then. I can handle teamwork. What do we need to do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_44">
		<text>I see.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_5">
		<text>The documents, that you stole from the military, mention a few secret places. Even though, they are highly encrypted I did manage to find the location of one of the secret facilities. It’s  lab by the name of x-18 located in Dark-Valley. Everything adds up, a secret laboratory was found in those parts. It's mentioned in the docs that a lot of the radioactive rubbish in Garbage came from x18.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_55">
		<text>Our target is the documents that haven't yet been recovered from the lab. According to what was already found out, it is most likely that the documents are in the lower floors. Even though there aren't many mutants there, you should still be very careful because of the high anomalous activity in that place. I suggest you get a good supply of meds before you go down there. Alright, I think that's all. So? Will you go for it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_6">
		<text>I see...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_66">
		<text>Alright then. If that’s all then I am going to go prepare for the trip.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_7">
		<text>In short, our target is the documents that haven’t been retrieved from the lab yet. The stalker, which already took the job once, didn't find anything. He’s here somewhere close, by the way. Try talk to him, he might give you some useful info. His name is Jeka dublet.   </text>
	</string>
	<string id="barman_tz_start_77">
		<text>Yeah, that’s all. Good luck out there. I expect you to come back alive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_0">
		<text>Слушай, а где сейчас этот Шустрый? Вроде среди «чистых» не встречал такого.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_1">
		<text> A tragedy has accorded. When we were moving to a new base because of the constant attacks carried out by the renegades, Nimble's health started acting up again. At the same time we started getting signals from the place where in 2011 we lost one of our assault squads. Nimble, along with another guy, insisted that we go and help whoever is calling for help but our commander, Vedrov, said that trying to help someone in our current condition is insane. When everyone was going to sleep, Nimble and that other guy snucked out of the base and headed somewhere. Sense then we couldn't find them. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_2">
		<text>Have they really disappeared without a trace?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_3">
		<text> Afraid so... Although, among the loners that work for us there were rumors that a stalker was spotted in Cordon with clear sky armor. According to these rumors he was working for Sidrovich. I doubt it's true though.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_4">
		<text> A sad turn of events indeed. If I'll ever pass through those parts then I will defiantly check it out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_44">
		<text>I’m sorry to hear that. Anyway, it’s been nice talking to you but I got to go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_5">
		<text> Yeah those rumors were probably baseless anyway. Either way, Thanks for hearing me out…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_nimble_quest_start_55">
		<text> Yeah, Of course. Feel free to comeback anytime and if you need anything repaired, I Am always up for the task.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_0">
		<text> are you free to talk? How did you end up here??</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_1">
		<text> There's not much to tell... When I was young, I used to work as a techiniton at the CNPP and after the accident I was left without a job. For a short time, I moved not far from the zone and made my living helping stalkers gear up for their trips.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_2">
		<text>Go on…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_3">
		<text> So, yeah, one time I provided gear for a young guy by name of Stephan. I managed to remember him for a long time because of his vast amount of enthusiasm and childish naivet?. It amazed me.  After a while, rumors started going around that a stalker managed to escape from an army patrol and that later he had gotten a fatal wound and fell in to an anomaly field. Back then, There weren't many stalkers and when I heard those rumors I started worrying about my friend. That's when I decided to go to the zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_4">
		<text>And what happened then, did you find Stephen?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_5">
		<text> You won't believe me, I found him, alive even.  When I found him he had a few bullet wounds and his clothes were all burnt up by an anomaly. He was still holding on with everything he had. I pulled him out of there and dragged him to the nearest camp I could find. We were in the swamps which back then I thought were abandoned But I was wrong. We were found by a few good dudes in blue armor, they fed us and saved Stephen life. We made friends with them. They told us they were from the Clear Sky faction and soon after that we decided to join them. Sense then, Stephen had managed to prove himself time after time and for his speed and stealth he was called Nimble.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_6">
		<text>Interesting story…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_tech_offtop_7">
		<text>Yeah! Anyway, back to work.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_0">
		<text>About your gang’s stash...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_1">
		<text>Don't pour salt in my wound... What did you bring? I shouldn't have told people about that stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_2">
		<text>The stash was left untouched. Perhaps someone should retrieve it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_3">
		<text>I don't need any of things there. I left that forsaken place right after I buried my dead friends. Although, wait, I remembered something!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_4">
		<text>What?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_5">
		<text> I forgotten something there, a note from my old friend, the one that guarded the stash. He wrote it a few minutes before his death. How could I forget something like this? Listen, stalker, I want that letter. Can you bring it to me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_6">
		<text> Suggesting that I go there and get that letter for you? Sure, I'll do it. Although, as payment, I want everything else in the stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_66">
		<text>I changed my mind. I have bigger things on my plate right now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_7">
		<text>Deal. Although, we sold most of our stuff after our last trip but there should be something valuable left. It's quite sufficient as payment. The stash is located at the watchtower not far the old clear sky base. Be careful though, the place is filled with radiation and anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_77">
		<text>See you later then.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_8">
		<text>Alright then, I’ll get there as soon as I’m ready.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_dialog_about_group_9">
		<text>Be careful.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_give_zapiska_0">
		<text>Greetings, I have found your letter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_give_zapiska_1">
		<text>Great news! Did everything go smooth?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_give_zapiska_2">
		<text> Hell, no. I was ambushed the second I stepped off the tower. My attackers wore sky blue sunrise suits and they didn't have any badges.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_give_zapiska_3">
		<text> What!? When I was checking up on that stash I did see bloodly bits of the suits you just descirbed. Who were those guys and what did we do to piss them off? God damn... </text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_give_zapiska_4">
		<text>I doubt they will bother you anytime soon. Anyway, here’s your friend’s note.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="death_give_zapiska_5">
		<text> Excellent, This is exactly what I was looking for. Here's some cash for a job well done. I know it's a small amount but I am on a tight budget right now. Good luck out there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_army_0">
		<text> Commander, sir, what’s going with our funding? Any news? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_army_1">
		<text>Payment is being held up, as always. However, There is a way you can get paid. I was sent a list of people we need to iliminate. I have strict order to pay anyone takes the task of removing any of these characters. Right now, we are sending out everyone who is willing to help with this task. It's simple: Kill any one of the people off this list and get paid.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_bandits_0">
		<text> Boss, People are saying that we have tracked a few rich stalkers and we have their position marked on a map. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_bandits_1">
		<text> Yeah, It's true. We track stalker's pda which pass through rich areas. Right now, I am giving out that software everyone so that they can find good loot without even leaving the camp. I am going to give that program to you too. Although, you should remember though, Part of the loot you collect goes to everyone else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_killer_0">
		<text>Any new contracts?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_killer_1">
		<text>Are you kidding? I got jobs up the ass right now and not enough people to do them. You feel me? You will be sent the whereabouts of your target, and once you eliminate them money will be sent to you as payment. Once one contract is complete, we will send you the location of your next target. I have already sent you the plugin for you pda, it's not hard to figure out. That's it, get to work.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_monolith_0">
		<text> Master, I have heard people are looking for alternative ways to reach the monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_monolith_1">
		<text> you are right, my disciple. All we can do is pray and fight the invaders. Our scientists have created a program for our pdas that help us track those who we think is dangerous to monolith. With its help we can stop any invasion. It goes without saying but anyone who helps in defending the monolith will be amply rewarded. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_sin_0">
		<text> Voron, I can't take it anymore! I think, I am going out of control. I have an uncontrollable urge to kill. text>
	</string>
	<string id="domino_sin_1">
		<text>
Hold it together! We can't allow ourselves to be reduced to such a low level. We have to kill with purpose, and only then we will be able to rid ourselves of this blood thirst and decadence. We have developed a program which helps us track stalkers who pose too much of threat, those who know too much about the zone. Their soulless bodies should be consumed by the zone. Only by helping her we can gain inner peace. As an encouragement, for every successful kill we will send you a small reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_0">
		<text>So, you are the local technician/</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_1">
		<text> Yeah, Sorta, Bro... I'm learning. Still can't do a full repair but I can do small repairs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_2">
		<text>So what is it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_3">
		<text> I made something really good, an upgraded PM. You can't find one like that anywhere else. Look! It can kill anyone better than a gauss rifle and I can give it to you for 250 rubles. You'll be doing me a favor testing it out in the field anyway.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_4">
		<text>250 rubles for a gun like that? Deal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_44">
		<text>What can of idiot do you take me for?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_5">
		<text> You won't regret it! Here. Sorry I didn't pack it up all nicely, I ran out of packing he-he...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drakoshin_pm_55">
		<text>Whatever you say...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_naparnik_start_0">
		<text>I’m ready.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_naparnik_start_1">
		<text>Excellent, Let’s go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_0">
		<text> Greetings, nomad. Are you the one who took the mission to find the documents?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_1">
		<text>How’s it any of your business? And do you know about it? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_2">
		<text>Take it easy, Barmen told me. Need any help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_3">
		<text>I suppose so…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_4">
		<text>I’ll help you. Tell about the mission in full detail.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_5">
		<text> Alright. Look here, the documents that we are looking for are, from what I was told, separated into two parts and are located in the lower floors. The lab itself is a very dangerous place, I saw it with my own eyes. Even though, the lower floors are mostly devoid of mutants there are still a shitload anomalies there. I couldn't even pass through there with my current protection. So? are you in?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_6">
		<text> Yeah. I’ll get to the lower levels, I have better gear. In the meantime you will keep watch while I look for the documents. Can you even shoot? He-he...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_66">
		<text>Alright buddy, Listen up. I’m doing this alone, I don’t want anyone getting in my way.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_666">
		<text>I’m not ready to do this, I’m cancelling the contract.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_7">
		<text> Don't worry dude, I've been around. Alright so the deal is sealed, We go there together. Gear up and come back here when you are ready.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_77">
		<text> Goddamn it, Keep the loot, just stop waving your gun around. You're lucky that there are lots of witnesses here. If we were in a different place, Things wouldn't have ended so quietly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duplet_start_777">
		<text>Alright, it’s your choice. Bye.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="events_give_agr_case_0">
		<text>I have an intriguing case here? Interested?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="events_give_agr_case_1">
		<text>Shhh.... Stop yelling! Where did you find this? Did you really steal it from the military? On the other hand, it doesn't really matter now. Slowly! And I mean slowly! Give me the case so nobody sees it and take your payment. Forget this thing ever existed, for your own safety. Got it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="events_give_case_sidor_0">
		<text>Waiting for the case? Here, maybe it’s this one?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="events_give_case_sidor_1">
		<text> Wait what, Where's nimble? What a lazy dipshit! What was I thinking hiring him? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="events_give_case_sidor_2">
		<text>If That’s the case then I’m keeping it for myself. Bye.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="events_give_case_sidor_3">
		<text> Wait! The hell with nimble, take his reward as well. You did the job, you deserve it. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_0">
		<text> Boss, I haven't been active lately. Is there any special mission that needs to be done?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_1">
		<text> You are just in time, man. There is a special task that I can only rely on a few to do right. So, fighter, ready to help anarchy?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_10">
		<text>Of course, There’s isn’t a job I’m not ready for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_py_start_dialog_100">
		<text>I’m not ready for a mission like that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_11">
		<text>Nice! Okay, let's get to business. First of all, Remember the password "Their product", without it the informant won't give you the needed info. Skinflint will give you something that will help get into the bar quietly. Also, I suggest you don't go to the bar through the northern gates. Rumor has it that the guards there are batshit insane and shoot everything that moves. After you get into the bar you are on your own. Be very careful and don't blow your cover, if you do, the mission will be compromised.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_110">
		<text What’s wrong? Are you afraid of those duty cowards? Alright, it’s your choice.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_2">
		<text>Ready.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_3">
		<text>I can’t hear you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_4">
		<text>Always ready, boss!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_5">
		<text>Now that's the spirit! Alright here's the deal: We have a spy in duty base, you probably know him, his the guy that sells information. Snitch is his name. He hires stalkers to send us info sometimes. Problem is he has went quite for some time now, no warning, no news, nothing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_6">
		<text>Alright, so my mission is…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_7">
		<text>Correct! You need to visit him personally and make everything is okay.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_8">
		<text>Umm… boss, How am I supposed get passed the duty? Are we planning an assault on the bar?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_spy_start_dialog_9">
		<text>No, we don't need any more bloodshed, now  a specially, when duty is on the defensive. My plan is this: Disguise yourself as a loner and walk in there quietly. Think you can handle that? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_0">
		<text>How did you get here?!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_1">
		<text> Oh, god! Please don't kill me. I.. I.. My team was ambushed... They took us here... You people are animals, you don't have a shred of humanity left... Your buddies took my partner and stuck him on a spike and then just watched him die. Degenerates! I will get out of here one day. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_2">
		<text> You better shut the fuck up Unless you want to end like your friend.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_3">
		<text>sor… sorry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_4">
		<text>What do you do in the outside world?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_5">
		<text> I'm a leader of a scientific expedition named after Carl Marx! My name is well known in the scientific community! I haven't yet lost one debate. My name is professor Frolov.!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_6">
		<text>You know what I think? Your meat is as shitty as your friend’s.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_about_7">
		<text>Don’t please… I beg you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_0">
		<text>Can you get me a repair kit?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_1">
		<text> Yes-yes, of course. Which type do you require? For a suit or for a gun? For a weapon repair kit I will take a "sinner's" currency, 3 tokens to be exact, as for the sewing kit - 500 rubles.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_2">
		<text>For weapons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_22">
		<text>For suits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_222">
		<text>Neither, I changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_3">
		<text>here you go, one repair kit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_33">
		<text>here you go, one sewing kit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gutorenko_remkomplekt_333">
		<text>Comeback anytime.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_0">
		<text>Can I ask a question?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_1">
		<text>Take a risk…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_2">
		<text>Why do you have such a weird nickname?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_22">
		<text>Can you tell me something interesting?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_222">
		<text>Labrador, one last question: where are the memes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_3">
		<text> Man... That's a sad story right there. When I was a kid I had a Labrador. I used to play with him at a lake near my house a specially in the fall when the ice was thin. I was a young kid back then and I didn't know any better. It's easy to figure what happened: I fell through the ice and my dog saved me. If it wasn't for him I would have drowned. Even though I came out unharmed my dog caught a lung infection, and our village didn't have veterinarians. Nobody knew how to help him and he died. So in his honor I named myself Labrador.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_33">
		<text>Have you heard anything about the war between SIIM and VGM?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_333">
		<text>The hell with it...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_4">
		<text>Got it. Thanks!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_44">
		<text>No, tell me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_5">
		<text>No problem.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_55">
		<text>SIIM are a research group whose full name has been long forgotten. They were formed during the very beginning, when the zone was starting to emerge. Here's the thing: This group has managed to make some kind of drug or a vaccine which dezombifes people and restores sanity to those fallen under the influence of the brain scorcher.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_66">
		<text>Okay and what happened?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_77">
		<text>VGM, SIIM's main competition, stole the recipe for this drug and took the credit for its creation. Once SIIM found about this, a war broke out between the two factions. They pretty much wiped each other out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_88">
		<text>Thanks, really interesting. Never heard this story before.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labrador_questions_99">
		<text>Yeah, I’m good at telling stories.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_1_0">
		<text>Can I help you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_1_1">
		<text>That would be great, although I don’t know with what. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_1_2">
		<text> Why are you not in contact with any other squads and why are you not trying to return to your base? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_1_3">
		<text>It's not that simple. No matter where we go, we end up in the same place. It seems as though we are trapped in some kind of spatial anomaly with no way out. Furthermore, despite this place having no exit, we are constantly attacked by mutants who appear out of nowhere. Talk to Kron, our technician, about this matter and he will tell you about our situation in full detail.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_2_0">
		<text>Hello. So tell me, in full detail, what the hell is going on here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_2_1">
		<text>If only I knew!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_2_2">
		<text>text in default</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lost_csky_dialog_2_3">
		<text>text in default</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_0">
		<text>Hello, Stephen.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_1">
		<text>Stalker, how do you know my name? Who the hell are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_2">
		<text> Relax. I traveled a long path to find you. Novikov sent me to find out how are you and his really worried about you.  </text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_3">
		<text> Novikov? I'm glad his alive and well. How's everyone else?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_4">
		<text> They’re doing fine. Sense your departure, your faction has moved to Medpribor and set up a new base there. You wanna visit your old friends by any chance?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_5">
		<text>No, friend, I don't want to return there. I've already made up my mind. I am glad to hear they are all alright though. Listen, if you decide to visit Clear Sky Tell Novikov that everything is alright with me and that I would love to meet up with him one day but right now I have to travel north.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_6">
		<text> Of course, I tell him when I'll be there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_dialog_7">
		<text> Thank you, stalker. You are a good person, I could tell straight away. Hey listen, I have contract I need complete and I need some assistance. If you want, you can help with it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_outfit_finish_0">
		<text>Is this the helmet? Doesn’t look like much. Here you go. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_outfit_finish_1">
		<text>Don't worry this will do just fine. Like my old friend used to say "If you will be happy with small victory, big ones will come on their own". Anyway, thanks and here’s your cut. It's not much but it's what I have right now. I would be happy to work with you again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_0">
		<text> Hey what's up? I've come with good news: Your friend, nimble, is alive and well! The rumors were true he really is in cordon working with Sidorovich.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_1">
		<text>No way…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_2">
		<text> Yeah, His alright. Although, he wouldn't tell what actually happened to him or why he won't return to clear sky.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_3">
		<text> I’m glad his alive!  We've been through so much together and many times have saved each other's lives. Did he say anything about coming back?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_4">
		<text>He doesn't want to talk about it. He said is not going to come back to clear sky and that is moving further north, deeper into the zone. However, he did say that he would be glad to meet up with you again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_5">
		<text> So that's how it is... Alright then. Either way, he is liked by the entire clan sense he contributed so much. And you, man, a big thanks from me and everyone else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_6">
		<text>Always glad to help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novikov_final_7">
		<text> You know what? I was saving up for a new and better pda but you earned it and don't you dare say no.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_0">
		<text>Hello.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_1">
		<text>And greetings to you. Do you wish to obtain some information or what? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_2">
		<text>Yeah, how’s “their product” doing?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_3">
		<text>Shh... Pipe down before someone hears you. Duty has been monitoring every inch, they must've caught on that someone is leaking information. That's why I couldn't contact your boss because duty has been listening in closely to every channel.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_4">
		<text>And where’s the loner that worked for you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_5">
		<text>Died somewhere I think, either from a blowout or a psi emission in Yanter. I don't know for sure, I received contradicting info. Something isn't right here, there's a chance duty caught on to him. Anyway, I will upload all the needed info to your pda and install a special protection, so no can hack it. Give the info to your boss personally. He will know how to bypass the protection.  Got it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_6">
		<text>Got it. Good luck to you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_spy_dialog_7">
		<text>Yeah, you too.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_0">
		<text>You mentioned a contract you need help with…</text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_1">
		<text> Not long ago, I was deep inside the zone, passed the bar, and don't ask how I managed to get there with such low-tier gear,  I hardly know myself. Anyway, the blowout was coming and I had to hide in some old basement which was filled with chemical anomalies. The smell there was just awful and the sand there was up to my knee. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_2">
		<text>Yeah, details, details. Get to the point.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_3">
		<text> Long story short, Inside the basement I found a bag and inside there was a strange armor similar to a mercenary suit but with light blue coloring like our old clear sky suits, a very interesting specimen indeed. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_4">
		<text>And?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_5">
		<text> Well, despite the good loot my trip ended badly and I barely got to Sidrovich. When I was treating my wounds, I decided to sell the armor. You won't imagine price I got for it and that's when it got me. What if I start finding suits, tweaking them a bit and then selling them for good money?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_6">
		<text>Hmm...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_7">
		<text>
I already found a good suit for sale but I need a helmet for it. When I was returning to the rookie village I was ambushed by bandits and I had to throw the helmet up on the roof of the grain elevator. Can you go it for me? It's probably still there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_8">
		<text> That's it? Can't you go it yourself? On the other hand, I don't really care as long as you pay.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="outfit_for_nimble_dialog_9">
		<text>Yeah-yeah I’ll pay, just go get the helmet. It’s urgent!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="saharok_after_brain_off_0">
		<text>The source of the psi-radiation has been neutralized.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="saharok_after_brain_off_1">
		<text>Excellent! You are in really good shape, despite surviving such a heavy strain on your nervous system. We have prepared a reward that's fitting to your contribution. This suit was made specifically for working in heavy anomalous fields, they are very expensive but you earned it. Once again, thank you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="saharok_docs_x16_0">
		<text>Greetings, Professor. I am here about Vedrov’s contract.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="saharok_docs_x16_1">
		<text> Ah, yes! You must be the stalker who found documents... It's so good that one of ours is doing this job. Did you take a peek inside the documents?  </text>
	</string>
	<string id="saharok_docs_x16_2">
		<text>I peeked a bit; I didn’t get much of it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="saharok_docs_x16_3">
		<text> Its better this way... What's in these documents is for me and my collogues eyes only. Big thanks for you effort! Vedrov told me to make sure you are rewarded properly for your work. Here you go...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_0">
		<text>Hello, Sidorovich. I am looking for someone and you might just know him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_1">
		<text>Greetings, stalker… And who might this person be?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_2">
		<text>His name is Nimble. I heard he’s working for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_3">
		<text>Let’s suppose I do, What Interest do you have in him? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_4">
		<text>I need to make sure he’s alive and deliver a message from some old friends.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_5">
		<text>Ahh… Clear sky? They’re good people. Are they still in one piece?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_6">
		<text>They moved their base to a different location. They are alive and healthy and are looking for nimble. So where is he?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_about_nimble_7">
		<text>He went on a mission just a minute ago. If you are lucky you can still catch him in the rookie village if you hurry. What are you waiting for? Go get him. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_case_finish_dialog_0">
		<text>What up, Skinflint? I haven’t come empty handed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_case_finish_dialog_1">
		<text>Great. You got the case?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_case_finish_dialog_2">
		<text>Here. Where’s the payment?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_case_finish_dialog_3">
		<text>wait a second! Let’s have a look first. Judging by the weight of the case there should be plenty of documents. As far as cracking the case, Shurup should handle it. You did good and you deserve to get paid well so here you go. You can leave the patches for yourself. They are useless anyway.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_0">
		<text>Hello, boss! I am back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_1">
		<text>Not bad, you’re back in one piece. Did everything go according to plan?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_2">
		<text>Yep. I met snitch, he give me the info. I’m uploading it to our server as we speak.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_3">
		<text>Good job. Anything else?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_4">
		<text>Duty has caught on that someone has been leaking info and they are already questioning snitch on it. The stalker that carried the info to us has probably been killed by the dutyers although there is a chance that he just died in an anomaly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_5">
		<text>So that’s why that stalker went silent. Anyway, here’s your reward and a personal gift from me for a job well done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_6">
		<text>Thanks, boss! Always glad to help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_quest_finish_dialog_7">
		<text>We are fighting for a free zone, remember that! Good work out there, keep fighting the good fight.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_0">
		<text>Good day, I’m here on important business.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_1">
		<text>Everybody comes here on business. What do you have?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_10">
		<text>What exactly do I need to get?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_11">
		<text>
a case which contains the results of some interesting research done by the scientists at Yantar. We have to get them before duty sends these papers to the government. You dig?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_12">
		<text>Sure. Any idea where this case located?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_13">
		<text> Somewhere in the bar area, in duty's base somewhere, we don't know where exactly. Sense duty often employs loners to do their dirty work you shouldn't have a problem getting in there. So? are you in?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_14">
		<text>Of course I’m in.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_15">
		<text>Alright, I’ll be waiting. Good luck out there and make sure not to get caught.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_2">
		<text>Alright, I need a loner patch. You have any?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_3">
		<text>Let’s say I do… Sense you are one of ours I’ll give you a discount, 1000 rubles. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_4">
		<text>No. How about I punch you in the face instead?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_5">
		<text>2000. Care to make another bid?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_6">
		<text> Man, you are a cheapskate! I'm not giving you any money sense the patch was requested by Miklukha for a special mission. so come on, fork it over.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_7">
		<text>You should have told me that in the first place... let’s see what I’ve got. Here you go, I hope it fits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_8">
		<text>Alright, enough fooling around. I have to go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="spy_skryaga_9">
		<text> That's the spirit! Hey, bring me back the patches when you are done with them. Hey, wait a second! Can you get me something? It will be a piece of cake with your new disguise.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_0">
		<text>I want to buy a stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_1">
		<text>Excellent. Here’s what I got.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_2">
		<text>Improved leather Jacket (1000 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_22">
		<text>anomalies leather jacket (1500 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_222">
		<text>Chainmail Jacket (2000 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_2222">
		<text>Tourist sunrise suit (2500 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_22222">
		<text>Enchanted suit (3000 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_222222">
		<text>Improved mercenary suit (3000 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_2222222">
		<text>Modified Hunter duty suit (4000 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_22222222">
		<text>Wind of freedom М2 (4000 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_222222222">
<text>Assault exoskeleton (20000 rub.)</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_3">
		<text>Are there any other stashes available?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_33">
		<text>There are. This stashes belong to dead stalkers so there’s no chance that the owner will come back for their loot. However there is a "but". I don't know what's in there. It could be garbage or it could be the best loot ever. There's isn't a way to know short of checking what's in there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_333">
		<text>I’ll take it (500 rub.)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_3333">
		<text>Nah, seems like a scam.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_444">
		<text>Okay, give me the cash and I will give you the coordinates… Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_4444">
		<text>Smart. I wouldn’t waste my money on it either.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_5">
		<text>I’ll think about it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_55">
		<text>Alright, but if you wanna buy a stash you better hurry. I have plenty of customers who want this info.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_6">
		<text>some time ago, the commander of the outpost in cordon was a guy by name of khaletskiy. He was dirty. He would leak stalker information to bandits, locations, paths and what not. The stalkers got sick of it and decided to teach him a lesson. They kidnapped him and put him in a cage. However, a mercenary, I forgot his name, helped him break out. He snuck a pistol and a special jacket that was supposed to protect him from mutants. During the night he killed the guard and managed to break out of the stalker camp. He died in mine field though, A sniper in the outpost thought he was a stalker and shot him. That special jacket is still there. Check for the mines with your bolts… Also, you should probably wait until the machine gunner leaves his post.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_66">
		<text> Do you know what tasty dishes Barman makes out of mutants? No? You're missing out. Barman had a stalker who would go to the swamp to hunt down small mutants for his dishes. Anyway, that stalker died in a chem anomaly somewhere in the swamps and if you have good chem protection you could go there and check it out. His gear should still be there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_666">
		<text>A bandit told me about this... The bandits had a guy who would modify their jackets. He would put armored plating in them and what not. However, all this modification weighed the jackets down and hence these mods did more harm than good. This guy though, thought he could prove to everyone that his mods are useful and took one of these jackets to Medpribor. Nobody heard from him sense. You can go there and check it out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_6666">
		<text> 
Man, have I got a story for you here! About a year back, when this war was only gaining traction, a stalker came to the zone. This guy had visited every place on the planet: The Alps, mount Everest, Sahara, Siberia, Amazon and many more. Get this though, he claimed that the best suit in the world was our sunrise suit that every common stalker wears. He bought his own sunrise suit from barmen and improved it in every aspect possible. I asked him what he was going to do with his old suit. I wanted to buy the suit off of him, I really liked it, but he told me he was planning to throw it on to a pile of rubbish in Garbage. Who knows, why he did it. If you plan to go there make sure to buy lots of antirads from Ern.... I mean Barman unless you want to die from radiation poisoning.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_66666">
		<text>
There was a stalker that used to hang out in the rookie village and there were rumors that he managed to escape from the Sinners. Nobody knows how but that's not what's important. According to the rumor, the guy, when he was held captive found out about how the sinners improve their armor. They throw their suits near an anomaly and wait for a few hours so that the anomaly can change the suit but not destroy it. Anyway, someone told that this guy found a fruit punch anomaly in dead valley and throw his suit in it. He will be happy to see you near his resting place.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_666666">
		<text>Listen here. Not long ago I got info that a squad of mercs died in Town-32. The last time the leader's pda was active was in the center of the city. After that, nothing was heard from them. But you're not interested in that are you? What's interesting though is that the leader of this band of mercs had a special duty suit... Don't look at me like that, when so much money is on the line everybody is suddenly your friend. Be careful though, Town-32 is a very dangerous place and only a few have comeback from there. Remember: don't follow the ghosts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_6666666">
		<text>Ok listen up. I've just got some info that one of duty's traders likes to buy weapons from the side. He bought and sold weapons pretty but he recently disappeared on a trip to one of his deals. I don't know what happened but that's not what matters. What matters is that he was going to sell a special PC3 suit. His stash should still be somewhere in darkscape where the suit is located. It's somewhere on the broken bridge there. Keep in my mind that duty likes hiding their things in high places so get ready to do some climbing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_66666666">
		<text>I have you met the freedom stalkers? One of those guys told me that something scary happened at their base in Bright Path. A sniper fell out of a window of a tall building all of a sudden. Some say that a controller took over him and made him jump. Others say that his family used to live in that building before they died and that PTSD took the best of him and he decided to end it all. Although that's not what's important, what's important is that he had a special freedom suit which everybody was jealous of. It's still there; those freedomers are very superstitious and are afraid to go get it. I hope you don't believe in all that bullshit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_666666666">
		<text>A serious order indeed. The previous owner of this exoskeleton was a serious guy... he was a friend of Strelok and a part of his team. nobody knew his name but everybody called him Gorbun. A strange guy, he constantly muttered things to himself but he was really crafty. He and Gromov made a special army exoskeleton using leaked blueprints from the military. It was one of the best armors I have ever seen. As a matter of fact it was so good that sidorovich came from cordon to find Gorbun and buy this suit. Gorbun however, declined the offer and hid the exoskeleton somewhere in wild territory, in the big metal structure near the downed helicopter to be exact. By the way Gorbun was killed by a mercenary somewhere north. But that's a different story.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_about_0">
		<text>Do you have any info on where I can find some rare loot?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_about_1">
		<text>Why wouldn’t I? Every day stalkers die and their stashes remain. I have lots of stash info.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_about_2">
		<text>And what’s in those stashes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toad_buy_outfits_about_3">
		<text> Unqiue suits in mint condition. So if you want something exotic to wear....</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_0">
		<text>Hi. Can you crack this pda?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_1">
		<text>That depends. Do you have any cash?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_2">
		<text>Don’t worry, I’ll pay.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_3">
		<text>You should have lead with that. Let’s see what you have and then we can talk about payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_4">
		<text>here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_5">
		<text> Okay, let's see what we have here... Wait, that's it? are you kidding me the password here was 1111... Was it that hard to figure out? Anyway, 5000 rubles and it's yours..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_6">
		<text>How about I punch you in the face instead? You haven’t done anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_7">
		<text>I did, I cracked it. 5000 ru please… </text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_8">
		<text>Enough bullshit. Either you give me the pda or I will… </text>
	</string>
	<string id="unblock_unknown_pda_9">
		<text>Alright-alright, take the damn pda and stop waving your gun around. Now get out of here and take your pda with you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vedrov_doc_dialog_0">
		<text>Hello, boss. What job do you have to offer?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vedrov_doc_dialog_1">
		<text> Okay, I won't hide anything. We are really understaffed. We don't even have enough people to guard the base and because of this we have to hire regular stalkers like you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vedrov_doc_dialog_2">
		<text>I have nothing against working for you as long as the pay is good.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vedrov_doc_dialog_3">
		<text>Oh the pay is great don't worry about that but the mission is difficult. So listen, it's not a secret anymore that in laboratory in lake Yanter experiments on the human mind were performed. I won't beat around the bush... We need the documentation of said experimentation. The documents should be split into 5 parts. These parts are located in different rooms throughout the lab.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vedrov_doc_dialog_4">
		<text>A difficult mission indeed but I’ll take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vedrov_doc_dialog_5">
		<text>Excellent. Once you complete your task, I will contact you.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>

