<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
<string id="red_forester_hello_dialog_0">
		<text>To what do I owe this pleasure?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_about_forest_0">
		<text>Tell me about the Red Forest.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_about_forest_1">
		<text>This used to be a wildlife reserve, and I was the local forester. I protected the forest and its animals from poachers. Now the Zone itself protects this place, and it does it so well that people are willing to travel a dozen extra miles just to avoid it. If a stranger sets his foot in the forest, he's as good as dead. I may be Forester, but even I don't know exactly what goes on here. A man walks into the mist and just gets sucked off into nowhere. You could be walking right behind him and still not know how he met his end. So that's that, sonny.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_about_zone_0">
		<text>What can you tell me about the Zone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_about_zone_1">
		<text>The Zone, heh... The Zone has a life of its own, and we people just get in its way - some more, some less. The Zone works to neutralize any risk to its existence the same way our bodies fight diseases. We get a fever, and the Zone has its shakes too. Emissions - now those are a way to "barf" us up. The more irritation we cause to it, the stronger the new emissions will be.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_about_zone_11">
		<text>How did you survive here all these years - alone and amidst all the dangers?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_about_zone_111">
		<text>One foolish action can destroy the Zone... along with everything that belongs to it. Not just mutants and anomalies, but also artefacts and you stalkers... and me. I can feel that the Zone is deeply concerned - something is upsetting it, disturbing its equilibrium. A storm is brewing... and I don't know if the status quo can be preserved. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_hello_dialog_1">
		<text>What's a rookie like you looking for in Forester's estate?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_hello_dialog_2">
		<text>Was it chance that brought you to me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_hello_dialog_3">
		<text>Good luck, son!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_hello_dialog_4">
		<text>Don't forget me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_hello_dialog_5">
		<text>Remember me well!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_who_are_you_0">
		<text>Who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_who_are_you_1">
		<text>What can I tell you about myself? I'm Forester. I've been here a long time; I've spent my whole life living next to this forest. I'm old. At my age you grow attached to your place of residence, no matter what it is. I refused to be evacuated after the accident at the power plant; I also survived the appearance of the Zone. I remember a flash on the horizon... many folks died that day, but the Zone spared me, you see? Heck, it didn't just spare me, it gave me a gift! I used to be able to find paths in the forest, and now I can feel a safe way of getting through real deadly anomalies. Stalkers envy me, but I can't say I'm all that happy about my gift. You must understand that everything comes at a price. Some day the Zone will take payment for my gift. That's what I am afraid of, buddy. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_who_are_you_111">
		<text>No, this was your typical pine forest. Well, it was also a nature reserve, but that was about as special as it got at the time. It became red after the accident at the Chernobyl NPP in 1986. It was green when I went to bed, and when I woke up it was as you see it now. Then the Zone appeared, and animals and birds abandoned this forest. I was the only living being that stayed behind. Just me, a red forest and this thick mist that never clears.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_forester_who_are_you_11111">
		<text>Yes, many stalkers have met their end here. I even heard rumours that an evil spirit lives in the Red Forest. The way I see it, this forest is just like everything else in the Zone. If you treat it right it won't touch you. The trouble is you stalkers don't treat anything right. You seek to own parts of the Zone and in return you get... what you're due.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="gutorenko_hello_dialog_0">
		<text>Don't shoot!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="kill_themall_0">
		<text>Is there any mission to be done?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="kill_themall_1">
		<text>There is. As a protector of the Zone, you must destroy those who represent Its threat. Kill them for the good of us and our lesser brothers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="kill_themall_2">
		<text>The mission is complete.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="kill_themall_3">
		<text>Excellent. Now, there will be better times to come for Sin.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="key_1">
		<text>Are there any special tasks?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_2">
		<text>Listen carefully: you need to find the Doctor in the swamps, take him down, and snatch a key from him. If you manage, there will be other tasks for you at hand.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_3">
		<text>Here is the key, as per your request.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_4">
		<text>Excellent. Here's the situation: our faction was once engaged in the manufacturing of gravity guns based on item number sixty-two under the name of Cerberus, but our only model was stolen by Strelok's group, along with the respective blueprints.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_5">
		<text>What do I need to do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_6">
		<text>Your task is to enter hotel Polissya in Pripyat, find room number twenty-six, and retrieve the gravity gun, together with its blueprints. Judging by my sources, a stash having formerly belonged to Strelok's group is located there. And, here. Take this psy-helmet; it will protect you from psy-emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_7">
		<text>I have retrieved the Cerberus model and its blueprints.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_8">
		<text>Well done, brother. Let's see...\n \n[checks blueprints]\n \nRemarkable...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_9">
		<text>Anything of interest?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_10">
		<text>Of interest? This is exactly what I had hoped to see. No longer shall this information fall into the wrong hands, and we shall restore the production of this weapon at once. You can keep the Cerberus; you've deserved it. Kurkul will be able to provide you with the ammunition necessary to operate such weaponry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="key_11">
		<text>Thank you. For Sin.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="old_sinner_0">
		<text>How can I help the brotherhood?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner_1">
		<text>A reliable source has come with some information. Duty is planning to seize part the Forest, going so far as to conscript free stalkers... The general is a naive idiot; he didn't even think to consider keeping this information private!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner_2">
		<text>What is my task?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner_3">
		<text>You must enrol in their ranks under the guise of an ordinary stalker and report back any information that you gather to me. This will provide your disguise. Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner_4">
		<text>Understood. I'm on the move.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="old_sinner_done_0">
		<text>The operation was a success; the squad of storm troopers has been liquidated. I was unable to escape without making some noise, though, and in the course of the operation, the leader of Duty and other inhabitants of the bar were killed. Morpheus and our other brothers—those who had been notified of my troubles from Shaman—came to my rescue.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner_done_1">
		<text>I am already aware, as Morpheus has notified me of the situation. You have displayed true devotion, bravery, and composure, and for that, I shall grant you one of two existing exoskeleton models we have: the Minotaur.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner_done_2">
		<text>Thank you. For Sin.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="old_sinner1_0">
		<text>We arrived just in time, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_1">
		<text>Not the word I'd use! And how did you know I'm here? How did you get here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_2">
		<text>It is all thanks to Shaman. He's said that a brother of ours has been waiting for trouble, and showed us a way underground to here, straight from the Bar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_3">
		<text>Who is that?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_4">
		<text>He is the eyes and ears of Sin. He is the one to whom we should give our gratitude for still breathing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_5">
		<text>Thank you, brothers! Where can I find Shaman, so that I may thank him personally?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_6">
		<text>According to our doctor Anubis, Shaman won't last for long... Go and see them. You may be helpful.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_7">
		<text>Where exactly is he?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_8">
		<text>I'll place a marker now... There.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="old_sinner1_9">
		<text>Thank you. I'll be moving.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_otryad_0">
		<text>Hello, stalker. I understand General Voronin has sent you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_otryad_1">
		<text>That is the case. What are our next steps?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_otryad_2">
		<text>We're standing by; got five minutes to prepare ourselves. After that, we'll be moving forward in the direction of the forest. Our orders are clear, and we'll be sticking together closely!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_otryad_3">
		<text>That you will! [laughter]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_otryad_4">
		<text>Huh? What's the matter with you? What the hell is going on here?!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="voronin_next_0">
		<text>Got a sitrep, sir!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="voronin_next_1">
		<text>Report at once, soldier! What has happened to the detachment?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="voronin_next_2">
		<text>They've all been killed. Traces of Sin have been found at the site of the incident; apparently, this is their handiwork.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="voronin_next_3">
		<text>Agh, you git! You didn't think I wouldn't see through that, did you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="voronin_next_4">
		<text>What do you mean, sir? I have nothing to do with this!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="voronin_next_5">
		<text>Show your true face, you wretched monster! Die!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="voronin_next_6">
		<text>...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_voronin_0">
		<text>Greetings, General!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_voronin_1">
		<text>Hello, stalker! What is the matter?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_voronin_2">
		<text>I've heard you're looking for experienced fighters for an assault on the Red Forest?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_voronin_3">
		<text>Indeed. You've arrived in the nick of time. The detachment carrying out the assault has set up camp in the vicinity of the old army warehouses and is waiting for further instructions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_voronin_4">
		<text>What are my orders?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_voronin_5">
		<text>Meet with the detachment and wait for any instructions from the commander. If anything changes, I'll let you know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_voronin_6">
		<text>Understood! Moving out.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="about_shaman_0">
		<text>Anubis, I presume?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_1">
		<text>Yes, that's me. What brings you here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_2">
		<text>I came to thank Shaman for saving me. Is he doing well?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_3">
		<text>For now, yes, but my efforts are barely enough to maintain his health, so... It's not even about how many days he can hold up anymore; hours, rather.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_4">
		<text>Can I help in any way?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_5">
		<text>You know... Yes, in fact. I have an idea that might be able to help him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_6">
		<text>I'm ready. What needs to be done?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_7">
		<text>You need to find a specific flower by the name of ‘black bat’. I already have everything else needed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_8">
		<text>Where can this ‘black bat flower’ be found?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_9">
		<text>The last time I saw one was in the vicinity of Jupiter, at the back of the plant. I saw it in a chemical anomaly. Didn't take it with me at the time, because I knew nothing about its properties...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_10">
		<text>I'll find it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_shaman_11">
		<text>I'll keep that in mind. It should help.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="anubis_bring_0">
		<text>I've returned, and not with empty hands.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="anubis_bring_1">
		<text>So you managed to find it? Give it here!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="anubis_bring_2">
		<text>Here you are. I hope you can put him back on his feet.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="anubis_bring_3">
		<text>Oh, I can't promise anything, but my chances have certainly gone up!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="shaman_thanks_0">
		<text>Thank you, brother. We're even now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="shaman_thanks_1">
		<text>Get well! Sin wouldn't be the same without your skills and expertise!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="shaman_thanks_2">
		<text>You know... I can't let you go from here empty-handed. Take this Gift of the Zone. It will make you stronger.<</text>
	</string>
	<string id="shaman_thanks_3">
		<text>Thank you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cresh_intro_0">
		<text>How may I serve the Monolith, brother?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cresh_intro_1">
		<text>We are having a few problems with the Brain Scorcher: it overheats too often, making additional cooling necessary, which means periodically turning off the installation. But we can not afford to shut down the installation for such periods of time, giving the infidels the possibility of breaking through to the great Monolith!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cresh_intro_2">
		<text>What do I need to do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cresh_intro_3">
		<text>There is a prototype of our installation in laboratory X-8, called the Rainbow, and our team is currently collecting data about the prototype... in hopes of understanding why the Brain Scorcher heats up to such extents. Make your way to the laboratory, receive the information from the detachment, and return it to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cresh_intro_0">
		<text>Moving out. Glory to the Monolith!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="neyron_intro_0">
		<text>...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="neyron_intro_1">
		<text>Brother! What's going on? What happened here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="neyron_intro_2">
		<text>Our detachment was studying the Raduga installation... We collected information for upgrading Duga-1, but the Sinners, curse them, showed up from who knows where... They slaughtered our entire detachment, and... agh, dammit... took the device with all our most recent information...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="neyron_intro_3">
		<text>Get up, brother. We must leave. I will get you out of here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="neyron_intro_4">
		<text>It's no use... I've lost too much blood... I can not offer you any more help. You must inform Charon of this at once and take action as soon as possible. Promise that you will avenge our fallen brothers... Monolith... I can see your radiance, Monolith...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="neyron_intro_5">
		<text>I will avenge you. They shall burn in hell.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="haron_intro_0">
		<text>Mentor, we've got problems. The unit that was engaged in researching Rainbow was taken out by members of Sin, and all the information collected for upgradinof the installation was also stolen.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_intro_1">
		<text>Damn these Sinner scum! So many brothers lost because of them... And it seems to me that a few rumours have been confirmed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_intro_2">
		<text>What do you mean?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_intro_3">
		<text>Right now, it does not matter. Our other brothers will take care of it. Your task right now is to storm the main base of the Sin in the Red Forest, and to search for any relevant information in that area. I will send a detachment of soldiers; they will wait for you at the northern outpost. Let the blood of all the infidels be shed!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_intro_4">
		<text>On it. Glory to the Monolith!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="haron_next_0">
		<text>The operation was a success. The infidels have been killed, just like their leader: the Crow. In addition, I found the PDA of Neuron, which was previously stolen by the Sinners. I also found Crow's documents and an unknown weapon sample, as well as blueprints for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_next_1">
		<text>... [examines documents]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_next_2">
		<text>What does it say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_next_3">
		<text>Evidence of rumours, which I have already mentioned... Sin does, in fact, haves a stalker who sees and hears all living things in the Zone... and he is known as Shaman. There is also a correspondence in these documents, which tells of the current location of Shaman, along with his partner, Anubis.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_next_4">
		<text>Where can I find them?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_next_5">
		<text>The exact place isn't indicated in the correspondence, but there's a tip-off that they've settled on the territory of the town of Svetly Put. I believe you know what needs to be done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_next_6">
		<text>I will send their bodies into the ground for the glory of the Monolith... but what about the unknown weapon?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_next_7">
		<text>Judging by the documents, this is the same Gauss rifle as the one we have, but with a slightly different power system. A good thing that you also managed to grab the blueprints for it, because without them, it's unlikely that the Sinners will have the chance of producing these weapons any further. And here, by the way, is your reward for your devotion to the Great Monolith!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="haron_complete_0">
		<text>Shaman is dead. Here is his PDA.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_complete_1">
		<text>Excellent. Without that freak in command, Sin will cease to be a threat to us. For your loyalty, you will rely on the very best equipment and ammunition we have! May the Force be with you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="haron_complete_2">
		<text>For the Monolith!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cresh_pda_0">
		<text>I've brought the PDA of the late Neuron, brother.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cresh_pda_1">
		<text>I've heard about what lengths you've gone to retrieve this PDA, and the Great Monolith blesses you! With this information, the Scorcher shall work with renewed vigour!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="avanger_intro_0">
		<text>Brethren, are you ready to take revenge on the infidels for our fallen?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="avanger_intro_1">
		<text>Yes! The Monolith shall be with us, brothers! Let us advance!</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
