<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="cit_doctor_hello_dialog_11">
        <text>Yes? What do you want? Strelok? Is that you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_hello_dialog_21">
        <text>What brings you here, friend?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_0">
        <text>Strelok? I think you’re confusing me with someone else, old man... Are you Doctor? I have a package for you from Sidorovich.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_1">
        <text>Someone else? Oh... Thanks for the package, though. Lugging everything around has gotten hard for me now, you know, so I have to send stalkers on errands. This is a collection of medicinal herbs, I make drugs out of them.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_11">
        <text>Sidorovich told me that you know a lot about the Zone. I’m preparing to go north. Can you tell me anything?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_2">
        <text>More than enough. I’ve had to be "on that side" of the Scorcher with a group of stalkers. Don't be surprised, there are many gaps, but not everyone can spot them! I've been stalking with others for a fairly long time, I’ve become close with my comrades. Only recently I’ve decided to settle down here in these marshes and heal everyone in need. And it doesn't matter if it’s a mutant or a human. I haven't discriminated between them for a long time.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_21">
        <text>You mentioned a group of stalkers... What’s happened to them?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_3">
        <text>They were trying to ascertain the cause of the Zone's appearance, they wanted to get inside the Sarcophagus, which they even managed to do. They and me were literally obsessed by this idea, especially our leader. When they were in the most dangerous places, I was providing reliable equipment for them. However, their last raid failed - nobody came back...</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_31">
        <text>How sad... But my interest is stronger than frightening stories. I’ll still make my way to the Zone's Center. Good luck, doc.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_4">
        <text>Wait! Don't go. If you’re going north no matter what... Find at least some information about my friends! They were called Strelok, Fang and Ghost. I haven't seen the latter two, but when Strelok was visiting me for the last time, he gave me a key and the coordinates for his stash in Pripyat. Surely there is something very important there. Here, take it, I have no use for it. It might help you in some way, at least.\nHe also mentioned something about the Monolith. I understood little of what he was saying then, and I'm not really convinced that he did either. What's more... He spent a lot of time searching for answers to the Zone’s secrets in underground laboratories. It’s not out of the question that some answers are still somewhere out there. I'll upload everything on your PDA, don't worry about it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_41">
        <text>Thanks a lot for the information and the key. If I find your friends, I’ll definitely bring back news.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cit_doctor_main_dialog_5">
        <text>Thank you. Have a safe trip, stalker...</text>
    </string>
    <string id="mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_start_dialog_1">
        <text>Need supplies or equipment? Information?... Or maybe you want to sell information?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_0">
        <text>I need medical assistance.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_1">
        <text>Alright, I'll see what I can do.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_11">
        <text>[continue...]</text>
    </string>
    <string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_111">
        <text>That wasn't so bad, eh? You can go.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_need_health_care_2">
        <text>Alright, I'll take a look... No wounds? You show no signs of radiation sickness. I think everything is in order; You are good to go.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_start_1">
        <text>Whatcha' need stalker?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_barmen_start_dialog_1">
        <text>A fresh face! People around here call me Librarian. I'm the local bartender. I'll be glad to answer any questions you have. Sometimes I post job offerings or hear some interesting rumours, so check back often.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_barmen_start_dialog_2">
        <text>Hey, stalker. What do you need?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_tech_start_1">
        <text>Greetings, stalker. Can I be of assistance? Good tools are hard to come by in the Zone, but I can still repair your kit and do minor upgrades.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_medic_background">
        <text>Me? I used to be a guide believe it or not. I mostly stuck to the marshes, but often took stalkers to places quite far from here. But that was a different time, before they found that damned mercenary in the reeds with a mouth full of swamp water.
		      Every single day he'd forget the way in and out of the base and I'd have to take him not more than a five minute walk from here to the fishing hamlet and back. And then within only a few weeks he'd somehow managed to convince our leadership and most of our men to charge into the power station.
			  Needless to say neither he nor much of our faction came back from his madness.\nBy the end of it I had nobody left to guide but plenty of people to patch up.\nSo here I am. All because of that fuckin' crazy merc.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_barman_background">
        <text>I'm the bartender. I serve drinks, food, and keep the radio playing. It's not an exciting job, but still preferable to being out in the field. Been working here for quite a few years now, got caught on the inside of the swamps when the emission hit so I was pretty much stuck here.
		      Headed south like most people tried to but I was one of the few that didn't get picked off by bandits on the way. I searched out this base and joined up with Clear Sky. It was either that or die in a puddle somewhere. Spent the first few weeks as a grunt repelling the anarchists from our lookout posts
			  and then got the job as the new bartender when Cold got promoted. Naturally I accepted, I'd rather be shooting drinks than bullets. But enough talk, how about a nice cold one?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_trader_background">
        <text>Spore's the name, I took over this gig about a year ago. Came to the Zone looking for wealth like everybody does and ran into a stalker called Nimble.\nFound out we shared a lot of the same talents, both got a lot of outside contacts,
		      good at trafficking goods in and out of the Zone, and selling info.\nSo when the Monolith resurgence happened and business was driven south, we followed. Managed to land myself a nice job here after Nimble recommended me to Cold. He was a member
			  of Clear Sky back in the day, y'know? Gives us both a nice little operation here, we have access to an army-free smuggling route through the swamps and Clear Sky gets first pick of everything we get our hands on. Pay Nimble a visit if you're ever
			  in the Cordon, last I heard he was hanging out around the rookie camp. If you ever need a hard to obtain weapon or outfit smuggled in from the outside he's the guy who peddles the goods.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_tech_background">
        <text>The name's Novikov, but some call me Grey. I'm the technician who keeps everything working, and the only person any good stalker goes to if their shooter starts jamming. Used to work here a long time ago until just before Cold took over. When everything went to shit I looked for somewhere greener
		      and got contracted by the Ecologists up in Jupiter. Was up there for a good few years until one day I heard that somehow these guys pulled through, and as soon as my contract was up I headed back. They took me in without question, my skills with a workbench and my contacts within the Ecologists
			  were sorely needed. I got us set up working with their guys so we could carry on with our old research. If you fancy the work they're always looking for guides to the local anomalies, talk to Spore about it if you're interested.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="marsh_stalker_leader_background">
        <text>Where do I begin? They call me Cold in these parts, I'm the leader of Clear Sky. Used to be the old drinks dispenser here a long time ago until I handed that honour over to Librarian once we caught wind of what happened to Lebedev, Suslov and the rest of our commanders.
		      After long and intense negotiations with the latest shipment of smuggled vodka, the local force decided that I was best suited for taking over the reins, and I've been holding on to them ever since.</text> 
    </string>
	<string id="marsh_csky_history_ask1">
		<text>Tell me about Clear Sky.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="marsh_csky_history_ask2">
		<text>What is it you want to know?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="marsh_csky_history_destroyed1">
		<text>Wasn't the faction destroyed?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="marsh_csky_history_destroyed2">
		<text>Almost, but we managed to pull through. While most of our guys were wiped out at the power plant, not all of us were. A good number were still in our other territories, which were later cut off from the rest of the Zone by anomalies following the emission.
		      When it became obvious to those in the swamps at the time that they were almost trapped here with no easy way out everything went to hell. Honest stalkers became bandits overnight whilst the rest tried to flee to our base or live off the area's mutants.
			  We took on a lot of men and our food stores ensured their loyalty, after a little while it became obvious we'd need a new leader. I took on the burden and asked our Librarian to man the bar in my place, he'd earned quite a name for himself in the short time since he joined.
			  After a few months of tit-for-tat raiding with the bandits we managed to smoke most of them out, but that didn't stop the army from feeling like they needed to move in and finish the job. Even now, they still have that bird of theirs watching the areas they took over.
			  </text>
	</string>

	<!-- Legend Returns -->
	<string id="greh_barter_1_0">
		<text>I need some equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_1">
		<text>I’ll trade it for stalker hearts. What do you need?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_9">
		<text>I don’t need anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_8">
		<text>I need a Recruitment Skull (7 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_7">
		<text>I need a ritual mask (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_6">
		<text>I need ammo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_555">
		<text>Let’s see here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5551">
		<text>I need shotgun ammo (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5552">
		<text>I need 5.45x39 ammo (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5553">
		<text>I need 9x18 ammo (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5554">
		<text>I need 9x19 ammo (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5555">
		<text>I need ammo for an anomalous Kalashnikov (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5556">
		<text>I need ammo for an anomalous shotgun (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5557">
		<text>I need ammo for an anomalous Colt (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5558">
		<text>I need grenades (5 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5559">
		<text>I need ammo for the "Cerberus" (5 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_5560">
		<text>I don’t need anything.</text>  
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_4">
		<text>I need armor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_333">
		<text>Let’s have a look.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_3331">
		<text>I’ll take a raincoat (5 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_3332">
		<text>I’ll take a reinforced raincoat (15 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_3333">
		<text>I’ll take an anomalous raincoat (30 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_3334">
		<text>I don’t need anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_2">
		<text>I need guns.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_222">
		<text>I need a "Ritual" knife (5 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_222">
		<text>Let’s see here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_21">
		<text>I’ll take a PM (2 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_22">
		<text>I’ll take a double-barreled shotgun (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_23">
		<text>I’ll take an AKS (5 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_24">
		<text>I’ll take an MP5 (5 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_25">
		<text>I’ll take an AKS-74 (7 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_26">
		<text>I’ll take a Chaser (7 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_27">
		<text>I’ll take an anomalous Colt (7 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_28">
		<text>I’ll take an anomalous AK (15 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_29">
		<text>I’ll take an anomalous pump action shotgun (15 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_30">
		<text>I’ll take a burned gun (7 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_1_299">
		<text>I don’t need anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_barter_3_0">
		<text>I need "speed" (3 hearts).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_story_start_0">
		<text>Got any special tasks?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_story_start_1">
		<text>Yes, I do. Have you heard how our vanguard died a few months ago at the CNPP?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_story_start_2">
		<text>Yes, I have.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_story_start_3">
		<text>Alright, my sources report that Strelok, the guy that our clan was chasing after, is still alive and is still hiding in the Zone. You need to search for him. Here, in the catacombs, judging by our old recon data, were at least two stashes. Try finding and examining them. Show me everything you've found. Without any unauthorized actions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_first_dialog_0">
		<text>Here, I found a PDA with messages sent between stalkers. Judging by its contents, they are his friends.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_first_dialog_1">
		<text>Let's see here... Hmm... There’s some simple cipher, that’s odd. What’s missing is the most important part. However, there’s a reference to Rostok with, let’s say, fresher messages. Obviously they were already suspicious of something back then. To be precise, there’s mention of an unfinished building. I think your next destination is clear, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_second_story_task_0">
		<text>I found it. And you can't even imagine what it took me. I was jumping around the factory’s roof like a boy from one garage to another.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_second_story_task_1">
		<text>Let’s take a look. Fucking hell! There’s nothing about his current location here too... But there’s one positive fact. While you were gone, I was asking around and found out that Strelok has had business relations with a trader in Cordon. Check that place out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_sidor_done_0">
		<text>Hello there, Sidorovich! Would you be so kind to let me ask about a certain stalker? He was dealing with you, and now I’m the one looking for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_sidor_done_1">
		<text>And who exactly are you interested in?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_sidor_done_2">
		<text>Strelok.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_sidor_done_3">
		<text>Look at that! I didn’t think I’d hear this again... Strelok isn’t a public person, however, I know how to help you. Let's do it like this: you do a few jobs for me and I’ll give you some info. Deal?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_sidor_done_4">
		<text>I have no choice. What do I have to do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_sidor_done_5">
		<text>There’s a certain stalker who left me without serious moolah. I need him to understand that he's done wrong... Capeesh? He goes by the name Miha Thief. And, according to my data, he's hiding somewhere in the northern part of the swamps.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="predatel_killed_0">
		<text>Ol’ Miha regretted his actions, and now you have to keep your side of the bargain.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="predatel_killed_1">
		<text>Ease up! I’m not some conman. If I said so, it means I’ll do it. So here’s what I'm gonna tell you. Strelok is in the Zone now. I have a guy who was following his signal for a while. However, he smelt trouble and did a bunk. The only thing left of him is his PDA, but it’s encrypted. Find a guy who will decrypt it. There'll surely be a lead, and not just one.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanik_unlock_0">
		<text>Hi! Mind helping me out? There’s a PDA that needs to be decrypted.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanik_unlock_1">
		<text>Hello there! I’m aware of your task, so I’ll do everything for free and to the best of my abilities. Let’s see... [Decrypting data] It’s ready. Let’s see here. Here’s the data it contains: "09:13 - I’m going after Strelok to the north. 14:23 - Strelok stopped in some small house, it seems that he’s decided to have a rest. 21:13 - He’s on the move again. 02:07 - We're somewhere in Zaton now, I have no idea where exactly... It’s too dark... 03:15 - He entered the Skadovsk. 12:28 - He hasn’t come out since. Looks like he’ll be staying here. 12:40 - I’m going to Sidorovich." That’s all.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_vedrov_0">
		<text>I have some news. Strelok, judging by the data on the PDA, is hiding somewhere in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_vedrov_1">
		<text>What are we waiting for then? He must be eliminated as soon as possible! Do it, we all depend on it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="strelok_killed_0">
		<text>Strelok is dead. I cannot believe it...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="strelok_killed_1">
		<text>Well done, stalker! Now we definitely know that Lebedev’s death was not in vain. By the way, while you were gone, one of the recon groups contacted us. They said that they'd saved a stalker from death and he had greatly helped Clear Sky back in the day. By the way, he also once made an attempt on Strelok’s life, but let’s not get off-topic here. So, we lost contact with the squad in Red Forest. We sent another squad after them, but it soon disappeared too. Your next task is to track down the squads.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="poisk_0">
		<text>I have bad news. I found just one fighter, and he too was dead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="poisk_1">
		<text>Goddammit! We’re losing men. They are some of the best... Were... Fine, let's drop it. What did he have?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="poisk_2">
		<text>I found a PDA on him, here it is. Maybe his info will shed some light on what's happened to his group.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="poisk_3">
		<text>[Reading data on the PDA] Let’s see... The group was attacked by unknown stalkers without insignia. It also says that the unknown men took one group member. That explains a lot. Your task is to return to Red Forest and find the survivor. I hope he’s still alive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="poisk_4">
		<text>Understood.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolozhit_0">
		<text>I'm back and I’ve got bad news again. I found the tunnel, but there was no stalker there. He had left a note there and it seems that he had dropped his PDA. But it’s broken and doesn’t work, I'll take it to Novikov, maybe he’ll be able to do something.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolozhit_1">
		<text>Alright. I’ll read the note, maybe I’ll find out more details.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_0">
		<text>Hi! I need your help again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_1">
		<text>What’s up, man. What do you want from me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_2">
		<text>Here's a PDA, it’s broken. I need any kind of information pried out from it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_3">
		<text>Let’s see... Whoa, it’s been almost completely smashed! Fine, I’ll try to do something. There’s nothing that I haven’t been able to deal with.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_4">
		<text>Thank you. Work your magic.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_5">
		<text>Let’s roll. Come on... Damn bastard! And what if we did this? There, it worked! It's busted as hell, but it seems like it still might work.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_6">
		<text>Well, what’s in it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_7">
		<text>Let’s see... It has notes with tasks, it seems like it's a merc’s PDA. Whoa! Now that’s something interesting... Among inactive tasks there are notes on the CNPP’s territory and a secret code. There are references to our former boss too - Lebedev. Let’s read more... Fucking hell! That’s it, the PDA’s dead, I can't get anything else out of it, don’t be angry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remont_8">
		<text>You helped out a lot anyway.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolozhit_vedrovy_0">
		<text>Novikov was able to get information out of it, there were notes with tasks, it was a merc’s PDA.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolozhit_vedrovy_1">
		<text>Excellent. Was anything else there?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolozhit_vedrovy_2">
		<text>Yes, he was at the CNPP and was somehow related to Lebedev.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolozhit_vedrovy_3">
		<text>My suspicions have been confirmed. It's him. He must be found immediately if he’s still alive! Go to Snitch right now, he’s in the Bar, and find out about the mercenary Scar. Got it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolozhit_vedrovy_4">
		<text>Mercenary Scar. Good, I’m moving out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_quest_dialog_0">
		<text>Hello, my good man! I need info about the current location of a certain stalker, and not an ordinary one. He's a merc.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_quest_dialog_1">
		<text>Hah, and you really need it? You guys have your head up your ass! What’s his name?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_quest_dialog_2">
		<text>He's known as Scar. The way I see it, I need money to get you talking? I happen to have it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_quest_dialog_3">
		<text>Scar?! Look, you don’t need to convince me, I agree anyway! I just happen to have information about him, but I’m not interested in money. I have a request. I had a, erm... good friend, but he disappeared not too long ago. His last message was from Jupiter Outskirts. Get hold of him for me, and you’ll get the info.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_quest_dialog_4">
		<text>And what brought him there?! Fine... What's his name?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_quest_dialog_5">
		<text>Stepan Fearless</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_info_next_0">
		<text>I’ve found your friend.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_info_next_1">
		<text>Well, what about him?!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_info_next_2">
		<text>He’s dead. He lived without fear and died without fear.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_info_next_3">
		<text>How could this happen?! Everything's fine and bam, this happens! He just up and died in full health! And he wasn’t a weak guy either. Anything else?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_info_next_4">
		<text>I found a PDA on him, but it's encrypted. Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="osvedomitel_info_next_5">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. I don't know the password for it. I don't have much information about Scar. Last time he was spotted at the northern passageways to the Swamps. He was acting extremely suspicious. He was clearly looking for a place to hide. That's the gist of it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_0">
		<text>Scar? Is that you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_1">
		<text>Mhm... And who are you? Yes, I really am Scar, but I don’t know you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_2">
		<text>I’m from "Clear Sky". The guys in Red Forest... Mind telling me what happened there?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_3">
		<text>Clear Sky?! I wasn't expecting that. Pardon the cold welcome, I didn’t recognize you immediately. Alright, listen: it doesn’t matter where I came back from, it's somewhere towards the army warehouses. However, I was caught in radiation near Radar, even if I had gone past it before without any problems. When I was close to death, I was picked up by "Clear Sky" members. Some time later, when I was nursed back to health, we decided to get out of there and go back to their camp, passing the Red Forest. However, while approaching the bridge, we were attacked by Sinners. We didn’t have any chances of winning. I tried to protect them, but to no avail. The boys were gunned down while I was shot in the legs and, it seems, I lost consciousness from the shock. I woke up in a tunnel where I left the note in case another squad went there, but later I managed to crawl out of there anyway. I found the guys who’d saved me on the way back, all dead. I feel sorry for them. Now YOU tell me what the hell is going on in the Swamps. Where is everyone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_4">
		<text>We've moved. Should I lead you to our base?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_5">
		<text>No, it's not worth it... I think I’ll stay here. I haven’t come back to my senses fully.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_6">
		<text>Suit yourself. Good luck, merc.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="start_shram_dialog_7">
		<text>Farewell, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="skazat_vedrovy_0">
		<text>I found him. He's in the Swamps. I invited him to our base, but he can’t come here yet - he’s healing his wounds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="skazat_vedrovy_1">
		<text>Don't sweat it. What’s important is that he’s alive. He was and still is a valuable asset. What else did you find out? What exactly happened in the forest?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="skazat_vedrovy_2">
		<text>They were attacked by Sinners. According to Scar, they were doomed... He was able to save himself, but with great difficulty.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="skazat_vedrovy_3">
		<text>Darn fanatics... How many lives they’ve ended, the assholes!...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="skazat_vedrovy_4">
		<text>What now?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="skazat_vedrovy_5">
		<text>Take this, you've fully earned it. You’ve greatly helped our cause. But now I want to be alone...</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
