<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_antirad">
		<text>Mexaminum</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_antirad_descr">
		<text>Radiation protection drugs are common in the Zone. When used, this drug induces contraction of peripheral blood vessels and oxygen deprivation, which serves to treat and prevent radiation exposure. The drug does not have severe side effects, although isolated cases of mild nausea, dizziness, cramps and stomach pain have been reported.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bandage">
		<text>Bandage</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bandage_descr">
		<text>A normal elastic bandage used to stop bleeding and prevent infection of wounds. For regular bleeding, carefully apply the bandage to the wound. For arterial bleeding, urgently tie the bandage around the affected area.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_binocular_descr">
		<text>Standard issue military binoculars with a maximum of x7.5 magnification. Useful in the Zone in that they allow its owner to observe things from a distance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_binocular_name">
		<text>Binoculars</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_descr">
		<text>Standard combat knife with a serrated blade. Useful for breaking open boxes and silently taking down enemies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife">
		<text>Bowie knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bread">
		<text>Bread</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bread_descr">
		<text>No bakers have ever been identified in the Zone, but this bread is neither contaminated nor radioactive, being fresh and quite edible. At least no complaints have been reported thus far.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_conserva">
		<text>"Tourist's Breakfast"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_conserva_descr">
		<text>Presumably, these canned goods were looted by stalkers from an army ration depot. Without any kind of label on the can, it's hard to say for sure. Should still be good to eat, if you believe the best before date.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector1">
		<text>"Echo" detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector1_descr">
		<text>This dated anomalous activity detector produces an alarm signal when anomalous particles enter a special chamber as you approach an anomaly. It can also register the presence of artefacts and measure the distance to the nearest one. The distance is indicated by the frequency of the sound the detector emits. To switch to artefact search mode, open the device's front cover. Due to its simple design, Echo can only be used to locate the most common artefacts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector2">
		<text>"Bear" detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector3">
		<text>"Veles" detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector3_descr">
		<text>A next generation scientific detection scanner. Thanks to three modernized detection chambers, the position of artefacts is shown on a special display screen. When closed, the device registers only radiation and anomalies. To switch to artefact search mode, open the front LED display. When in search mode, the detector is capable of locating all artefacts known to science.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector4">
		<text>"Svarog" detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector4_descr">
		<text>A prototype of an expanded functionality anomalous frequency scanner. This device comes with a program used to identify static areas of anomalous activity stored in its database, while retaining the ability to locate artefacts. The position of anomalous areas and artefacts is displayed on a special screen. The artefact search mode, which can be activated by opening the front LED display, has been modified to detect anomalous formations currently unknown to science.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_descr">
		<text>A standard head-mounted flashlight. Useful for stalkers who find themselves out and about after dark, but may attract trouble if used unwisely.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_name">
		<text>Flashlight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_anabiotic">
		<text>Anabiotics</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_antidot">
		<text>IP2 antitoxin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_antidot_descr">
		<text>A complex drug comprising several antidotes, including metoclopramidum, pyridoxine, thiamine, riboxin and other pharmaceuticals. The drug is used to inject a range of antibiotics to neutralize natural poisons, together with synthetic poison absorbers, into the bloodstream. IP2 is not particularly popular in the Zone, as most stalkers rely on a gas mask and a protective suit, there are still those who have a pack of this antidote stashed away. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_booster">
		<text>Hercules</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_coagulant">
		<text>Vikasolum</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_coagulant_descr">
		<text>An artificial equivalent of vitamin K. The main purpose of this drug is to increase blood coagulation speed. In great demand among stalkers who want slow-healing wounds and lacerations inflicted by mutants to close up faster. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_psy_blockade">
		<text>Psi-block</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_psy_blockade_descr">
		<text>A drug that blocks avalanche-like nerve impulses. Consumption induces short-term loss of all emotion. Used exclusively in the Zone to counteract the effects of anomalous psi-fields. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_radioprotector">
		<text>B190 Indraline</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_energy_drink">
		<text>Non Stop energy drink</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_energy_drink_descr">
		<text>Often used by stalkers on long trips when no breaks can be afforded. The drink contains easily digestible carbohydrates, as well as drugs that stimulate the release of adrenaline into the bloodstream.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_guitar_descr">
		<text>A trusty guitar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_guitar_name">
		<text>Guitar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_kolbasa">
		<text>Diet sausage</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_kolbasa_descr">
		<text>For better or worse, this sausage - a mix of chicken and a soy substitute - is often a stalker's breakfast, lunch and dinner in one. Can be stored for a long time due to high preservative content.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medkit">
		<text>Diagnostic first-aid kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medkit_army">
		<text>Army medkit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medkit_army_descr">
		<text>A specialized medical kit for providing first aid to combat casualties. The kit includes blood coagulants based on menadione, painkillers, antibiotics and immunostimulants, as well as a kit for removing bullets and fragments from the body. This medkit is issued to army personnel as standard and is sometimes used by Duty forces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medkit_descr">
		<text>A general purpose medical kit with a HEALTH-13 type injector. Handy for treating various injuries - wounds, bruises, regular and chemical burns and various types of poisoning. In demand among stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medkit_science">
		<text>Scientific medkit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medkit_science_descr">
		<text>A medical kit designed specifically for use in the Zone. The kit contains products for handling wounds, as well as preventing the development of radiation poisoning and reducing accumulated radiation in the body. Contains Vikasolum, Batilolum and Naphazoline, unlike other medkits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_descr">
		<text>Might have useful information on it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_spore_name">
		<text>Spore's PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_vodka">
		<text>Cossacks Vodka</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_vodka_descr">
		<text>Made by GSC. Goes down easy and considerably lowers the effects of radiation. Should be enjoyed in moderation.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector2_descr">
		<text>This last generation anomalous activity detector can be used to locate anomalous formations and has a colour diode panel, which not only indicates the direction of artefacts, but also measures the distance to them. To switch to artefact search mode, open the device's front cover. Unfortunately, the device is programmed with a somewhat outdated list of detectable artefacts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_anabiotic_descr">
		<text>An experimental drug developed by Professor Ozersky for scientific research teams working in the Zone. At its core, the drug contains tetrodotoxin, known colloquially as "zombie powder," which causes a complete shutdown of the body's central nervous system that may allow people to survive emissions outside cover. The drug has not undergone clinical or field testing, which puts its effectiveness in doubt and raises the issue of possible side effects.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bolt">
		<text>Bolt</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_booster_descr">
		<text>The main component of this product is an anabolic androgen, an artificial steroid, the chemical composition of which resembles testosterone. Often used by stalkers during long raids to reduce muscle fatigue. Significantly increases weight-carrying capacity. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_radioprotector_descr">
		<text>A radioprotectant, included in medkits issued to nuclear power plant personnel. Used in the Zone instead of the excessively toxic PC1 cystamine hydrochloride, repeated use of which often caused death. Reduces the effects of gamma radiation on live tissue. Best consumed before exposure, as effects are not instant. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_harmonica_name">
		<text>Harmonica</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_harmonica_descr">
		<text>For blues and prison romance lovers.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_deployable_mgun_name">
		<text>Deployable RP-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_deployable_mgun_desc">
		<text>This belt-fed machine gun is a portable modification with a complex two-stage feeding system. Despite its weight and low precision, this LMG has found admirers in the Zone. Used primarily to fight off outnumbering enemy forces during faction conflicts and clear out mutant lairs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_memory_stick_name">
		<text>Memory stick</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_backpack_name">
		<text>Backpack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_backpack_desc">
		<text>A regular water resistant backpack. It has high popularity among stalkers who travel around the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_smallpack_name">
		<text>Small backpack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_smallpack_desc">
		<text>Small backpack usually worn by rookies. The inside has been modified to keep water out. Not a pretty solution, but it works.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_milpack_name">
		<text>Combat backpack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_milpack_desc">
		<text>A combat backpack used by the military, often to store additional munitions and medical supplies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_touristpack_name">
		<text>Tourist backpack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equ_touristpack_desc">
		<text>A tourist's backpack with a lot of storage space. Not very popular due to its cumbersome size.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Legend Returns -->
	<string id="st_knife_greh">
		<text>Warg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_greh_descr">
		<text>Used by the Sin group for conducting rituals and sacrifices.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="sinner_spawn">
		<text>Invocatory Skull</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sinner_spawn_descr">
		<text>Used by "Sinners" to invoke mutants. Leeches off health from the user when activated.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pills_name">
		<text>Medical capsule</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pills_descr">
		<text>A complex of inexpensive drugs that stimulates the body's physical activity. May cause mental dependence, insomnia, anorexia, irritability, sometimes tachycardia and increased blood pressure. Chronic abuse of these pills might cause stimulant psychosis...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="water_name">
		<text>Mineral water</text>
	</string>
	<string id="water_descr">
		<text>Pure natural water, which contains microelements, dissolved salts and biologically active components. Perfectly quenches thirst and cleanses the body.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="vegetables_name">
		<text>"Bonduelle" Vegetables</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vegetables_descr">
		<text>Delicious canned vegetable salad of French production. Natural product. Exclusively for stalkers-gourmets.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_amphetamin">
		<text>Amphetamine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_amphetamin_descr">
		<text>Amphetamine (short of methylphenylethylamine) is a stimulant of the central nervous system. The mechanism of action is based on the release of neurotransmitters (dopamine and noradrenaline). Used by stalkers in multi-day outings</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lsd">
		<text>LSD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lsd_descr">
		<text>Semisynthetic psychoactive substance from the family of ergoline. LSD can be considered the most famous psychedelic, often used as a recreational drug and for spiritual reasons.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_memory_stick_name">
		<text>Memory card</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_heart">
		<text>Heart of a stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_heart_descr">
		<text>A heart that once belonged to a stalker. You can exchange it for equipment from a merchant of the Sin faction.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_brain">
		<text>Brain of a stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_brain_descr">
		<text>A brain that once belonged to a stalker. It is used by "Sinners" as food and is used by them in sacrifices. However, normal stalkers have this "delicacy" strictly prohibited. Side effects: dizziness, nausea, diarrhea, Guro's disease. </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_eye">
		<text>Eye of a stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_eye_descr">
		<text>An eye that once belonged to a stalker. It is used by "Sinners" as food and is used by them in sacrifices. However, normal stalkers have this "delicacy" strictly prohibited. Side effects: dizziness, nausea, diarrhea, Guro's disease.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_uho">
		<text>Ear of a stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_uho_descr">
		<text>An ear that once belonged to a stalker. It is used by "Sinners" as food and is used by them in sacrifices. However, normal stalkers have this "delicacy" strictly prohibited. Side effects: dizziness, nausea, diarrhea, Guro's disease.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_liver">
		<text>Liver of a stalker </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_liver_descr">
		<text>A liver that once belonged to a stalker. It is used by "Sinners" as food and is used by them in sacrifices. However, normal stalkers have this "delicacy" strictly prohibited. Side effects: dizziness, nausea, diarrhea, Guro's disease.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_finger">
		<text>Finger of stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_finger_descr">
		<text>A brain that once belonged to a stalker. It is used by "Sinners" as food and is used by them in sacrifices. However, normal stalkers have this "delicacy" strictly prohibited. Side effects: dizziness, nausea, diarrhea, Guro's disease.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="strelok_friends_pda_name">
		<text>PDA containing the correspondence of Strelok's friends</text>
	</string>
	<string id="strelok_friends_pda_descr">
		<text>This PDA contains the following correspondence:\n \n«— Hello! Did you leave a note for Strelok?\n— Yes, in Rostok, he knows where. In the unfinished building, as always.\n— Well then, okay, we'll meet at our place and discuss everything there.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="sidor_informer_pda_locked_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sidor_informer_pda_locked_descr">
		<text>No access.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="strelok_perepiska_name">
		<text>Note for Strelok</text>
	</string>
	<string id="strelok_perepiska_descr">
		<text>Strelok, we learned everything about that stalker, we'll tell you when we meet, you know where. We also left you some food and medicines in the second cache.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pda_leader_name">
		<text>PDA of the reconnaissance squad's leader</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pda_leader_descr">
		<text>His last note: "01:13 We are heading through the Red Forest. 01:23 We are attacked by a group of unknown people, we won't last long, we'll hide the stalker in the tunnel.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zapiska_shrama_name">
		<text>Note of the unknown</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zapiska_shrama_descr">
		<text>I woke up in some tunnel, the stalkers from the detachment of Clear Sky are missing, I will now finish this note and move forward...\n \n The note suddenly stops.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pda_stepana_name">
		<text>PDA of Stepan Fearless</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pda_stepana_descr">
		<text>All the data is encrypted.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pda_shrama_name">
		<text>Unknown PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pda_shrama_descr">
		<text>This PDA is broken, all info is irrecoverable.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- LONER'S PDA -->
	<string id="st_stalker_novice_pda_name">
		<text>PDA of a stalker. Rank - Novice</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stalker_novice_pda_descr">
		<text>PDA of a novice stalker. Traders will probably buy it for maximum of %c[default]%c[110,0,128,64]300 rubles%c[default], since there is nothing interesting on it.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_stalker_experienced_pda_name">
		<text>PDA of a stalker. Rank - Experienced</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stalker_experienced_pda_descr">
		<text>PDA of an experienced stalker. Traders will probably offer %c[default]%c[0,100,100,0]500 rubles for it.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_sever_case_name">
		<text>Briefcase with a combination lock</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_sever_case_descr">
		<text>Briefcase with a combination lock, quite heavy. According to Owl, it is full of radio parts for a technician.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_escape_docs_name">
		<text>Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_escape_docs_descr">
		<text>Documents detailing military plans about seizing the southern territories of the Zone. Sidorovich considers them of exceptional value.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="escpae_sidor_case_descr">
		<text>Briefcase with a combination lock, Sidorovich considers it of exceptional value.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Monolith storyline -->
	<string id="gauss_cont">
		<text>Case (can be opened)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gauss_cont_descr">
		<text>Heavy container, sounds like it contains a weapon of fearsome size. It can be opened.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="killer_x16_pda_name">
		<text>PDA of a Mercenary</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_x16_pda_descr">
		<text>The PDA contains an unsent message: "Commander, the psi-helmet is starting to act up, it will require repairs and extensive tests in the lab. But I'll hide the docs where..." The message ends.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_x16_docs_name">
		<text>Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_x16_docs_descr">
		<text>These documents are of exceptional value to Dushman.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killers_radiocase_descr">
		<text>The case with the radio equipment, carries exceptional value for Dushman.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Bohr's -->
	<string id="boyarushnik">
		<text>Tincture</text>
	</string>
	<string id="boyarushnik_descr">
		<text>Tincture containing various herbs and "Cortinarius arboricola"</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
