<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker">
		<text>Loner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker_desc">
		<text>Free stalkers are drawn to the Zone of Alienation for a variety of reasons: enrichment, thirst for adventure, the urge to learn the unknown, the desire to make a fresh start. Generally, in all specific cases, all these factors act simultaneously. Most of them do not tolerate any kind of control and prefer to be the masters of themselves, without even communicating with the rest of the stalkers, while maintaining a neutral relationship with all groups. The main source of income for stalkers is looting: artifacts, parts of monsters, weapons and items of dead stalkers. Often very profitable may be the fulfillment of different tasks given by traders, scientists or faction leaders, among others.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit">
		<text>Bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit_desc">
		<text>Representatives of the criminal world who came to the Zone for various reasons: to earn on the sale of artifacts, hide from the law, buy or sell weapons. Most of them are united in gangs. Although there is still no major gangster organization in the Zone, they are a great bother to ordinary stalkers - they make those pay them "tributes". Their main activities - murder, robbery, extortion. They are divided into disparate clans (often hostile). They, according to their assertion, protect single persons - and they must pay them. Ordinary racket. They, like Duty, have an unspoken code - "ideas" (however, this does not really help stalkers). There are rumors that the bandits are working for the Syndicate, and even collaborate with anarchists. As such, they do not have a single leader, but the most authoritative leader is Borov, who rallied his gang in a well-fortified base in the Dead Valley.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg">
		<text>Duty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg_desc">
		<text>Stalker faction, a militarized volunteer army, whose goal is to fight and suppress the Zone. They consider it their duty to protect the world from the invasion of mutants. Destroy the nests and mutant hives. They consider themselves Chernobyl witchers and vampire hunters. Its members live according to strict military regulations. It is distinguished by a rather strict discipline and military attributes. In the Duty faction its soldiers are divided using military ranks. Duty also deals with the internal problems of the Zone, such as the destruction of mutants, bandits and dissident anarchists in the face of a group, called Freedom. The main forces are concentrated on the territory of Rostock, next to the 100 Rads Bar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom">
		<text>Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom_desc">
		<text>Anarchists and daredevils, fighters for freedom from any control. They fight against the army and the government, their goal is making the Zone a free reserve. They strongly believe that information about what is happening in the Zone should be known to everyone. Freedom members believe that the Zone can't be defeated, it's only possible to agree with it. The Zone, according to their ideals, is a good object for research and study and it should in no way be a "beachhead for the military". That is why Freedom is trying to free the Zone from the control of corporations and the government. Also, Freedom believes that the Zone can not be hidden from the rest of the world. In this faction there is no strict discipline, there is equality, but there is a certain military connection between the participants, although it is strongly veiled. Lengthy and fiercely in conflict with Duty due to a variety of reasons. The main haven of these anarchists is the town of Bright Way, where they are firmly entrenched.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army">
		<text>Military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army_desc">
		<text>A contingent of the Armed Forces of Ukraine located in the Zone and adjacent territories, which performs numerous functions for the protection of the Zone, escorting scientific research expeditions, shooting mutated animals and bandits, etc. They are servicemen of the State Security Service of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine and special purpose units of the Security Service of Ukraine. They are the only representatives of official state power on the territory of the Zone, and therefore consider themselves placed above all other inhabitants of the Zone. Usually their actions are guided by military regulations and orders of the authorities. However, there are cases when some officers and sergeants receive bribes from stalkers for certain services. The corps of the AFU inside the Zone is located in the building of the Institute of Research Institute "Medpribor"; another zone of influence of the army is Cordon, where many army checkpoints are located.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog">
		<text>Ecologist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog_desc">
		<text>Individual research groups operating in the Chernobyl Exclusion Zone, financed by the state. They are engaged in studying the Zone as a whole, and all its manifestations in particular. Despite the fact that they try to stay away from conflicts between stalkers, they are often forced into it by force, which makes the entire expedition suffer. Nevertheless, they have powerful patronage of the Ukrainian military and Duty. Their main bases are specially equipped and sealed mobile bunker labs with small tinted windows, delivered directly into the Zone by cargo helicopters. These bunkers can withstand almost any kind of damage known to man. They can be transferred to a completely autonomous mode for several months, for which they are equipped with reliable life support systems. The leading scientific expedition headed by Prof. Sakharov is located on the territory of Lake Yantar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer">
		<text>Mercenary</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer_desc">
		<text>Nothing personal - just money. Someone constantly uses the services of mercenaries: professionals in their field, they will quickly deal with any stalker and they can easily dispatch small groups. They know the Zone worse than the usual tramp and often die where some rookie would notice the danger, but as far as war with people is concerned, they are absolute masters. And for their services, apparently, they take considerable sums in money or artifacts. Among the mercenaries are often representatives of PMC, including groups of foreign special forces. The history of the Syndicate is shrouded in mystery. Separate small groups appeared almost from the very beginning of the Zone for carrying out large orders "from outside." Their main base, presumably, is next to the army warehouses - on the territory that the stalkers call Silent Hills.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith">
		<text>Monolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith_desc">
		<text>A religious sect, rather than a faction. Its members believe that in the center of the Zone lies an evolutionary crystal - the Monolith - of unearthly origin. Most stalkers despise the followers of the "Monolith", considering them insane. Since its inception, the group has prevented stalkers from reaching center of the Zone, citing the ill intentions of the latter in relation to the Monolith. Enmity with the group "Sin" on religious grounds. The main refuge of these sectarians is a ghost town - Pripyat. They also keep the approaches to the Brain Scorcher from unwanted intruders.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky">
		<text>Clear Sky</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky_desc">
		<text>A highly secretive group composed of peculiar stalkers-ecologists. They study the Zone, looking for a method to heal the world from this ulcer. They possess good knowledge of the Zone and know how to avoid anomalies. They struggle badly because of their limited experience of military actions (on average) and rather mediocre weapons, but any paramilitary group can envy their technologies. Because of their ideology, they cooperate closely with the Duty faction, as well as with research groups. Their temporary shelter has recently been the production buildings on the territory of Medpribor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_zombied">
		<text>Zombified</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_zombied_desc">
		<text>%c[0,245,245,220]Braaaiiinnnsss!!!\n \nZombified stalkers are mindless husks of their previous selves reduced to their most basic animal-like instincts and will attack almost anything that gets too close.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_back">
		<text>Back</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_submit">
		<text>Start</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_rand">
		<text>Randomize</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_character_name">
		<text>Name:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_cap_faction">
		<text>Faction:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_ck_story_desc">
		<text>
			%c[0,245,245,220]You are trying to solve the riddle of the origin of the Zone. To do this, you venture on a trip full of dangers, which may be the last for you. Your starting point is the bunker of Sidorovich, the local merchant in the Cordon. Can you defeat an unknown force, or will you be cast into oblivion?\n
			\nOnly available to Loner, Duty, Freedom, Ecologist, Mercenary, Clear Sky and Black Slugs factions.\n
			\nThe storyline is not compatible with the Ironman mode.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_ck_hardcore_desc">
		<text>
			%c[0,245,245,220]Ironman mode is a feature that will remove your game saves upon death.\n
			\nYou are free to make as many saves as you wish but dying will result in the removal of all saves made with this character.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_ck_hardcore_aim_desc">
		<text>
			%c[0,245,245,220]Hardcore AI Aim is a feature that maximizes AI aim predictability, making it more difficult for the player to dodge hits while moving.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_ck_survival_desc">
		<text>
			%c[0,245,245,220]Survival mode is a feature that replaces all spawns with Zombies.\n
			\nThese hordes will make their way to your location - be prepared! See how long you can survive!
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_ck_azazel_mode_desc">
		<text>
			%c[0,245,245,220]In Azazel mode, death is not the end.\n
			\nLike the demon Azazel you will possess a new body when you die; taking over the form of another random stalker that really exists in the Zone.\n
			\nIf you have companions, you will become one of them. This feature compliments Ironman and/or Survival mode very well.\n
			\nNot compatible with Story mode.
		</text>
	</string>
	<!-- LR ADDED -->
	<string id="st_cap_check_long_skills">
		<text>Long haul</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_ck_long_skills_desc">
		<text>
			%c[0,245,245,220]There are those who play for a very long periods of time, for example until they gather all possible achievements. If you are one of these people, this is the mode for you. In this mode, you can reach the maximum level only when you attain 50,000 experience points.
		</text>
	</string>
	<!-- LR ADDED -->
	<string id="st_mm_faction_random_location">
		<text>Random Location</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_faction_money">
		<text>Money</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_equipment">
		<text>Equipment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_faction_relations">
		<text>Relations</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
