<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<!-- FIND WEAPON FOR NIMBLE TASK -->
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_name">
		<text>Find "%s"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_text">
		<text>Nimble has asked you to find a specific firearm. It needs to be in mint condition. Return to him when you find what he is looking for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_about">
		<text>I have a client looking for a specific firearm and I need someone to help me find it. If you are interested I will give you more details. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>%s... That is what I need, but it must be in mint condition. The client is paying top dollar and he doesn't want a rusty piece of shit that will jam up in a life or death situation. I'll give you most of the profit since you are doing all the work. Come back when you find it, man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>This is a fine weapon. I think my client will be pleased when I deliver this to him. Here is what I owe you.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- ASSAULT BANDIT BASE FOR SIDOROVICH TASK -->
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_name">
		<text>Massacre</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_text">
		<text>Eliminate a group of indebted stalkers that are hiding among the Black Slugs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>Once again I have the proof that is never a good thing doing good for free! Some finches here promised me a lot of artifacts from the Garbage in exchange for weapons and equipment; they indebted themselves, to put it mildly, up to their ears, and now interests are piling up! Purely out of principle - help me deal with them! They are now hiding in the ranks of the Black Slugs. I'll be paying you good money for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_finish">
		<text>Good job. A good job deserves a good reward.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- ASSASSINATION FOR SIDOROVICH TASK -->
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_name">
		<text>Contract killer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_text">
		<text>Sidorovich contracted you to run a hit. Find and eliminate the target then return to Sidorovich for payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_about">
		<text>I have a list of outstanding bounties and stalkers that need taken care of. The worst kind of scum and villainy usually end up on this list... For various reasons. The Zone needs its trash taken out from time to time. What do you say, stalker, will you be my hired gun?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_finish">
		<text>Good, you got rid of that asshole! Here is what I promised.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- ELIMINATE MUTANTS FOR WOLF TASK -->
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_name">
		<text>Clear area of mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_text">
		<text>Wolf asked you to purge an area of all mutant threats in order to ensure the safety of rookie village; as well as the stalkers who pass through Cordon. Reach the location and eliminate all mutants around the area. Return to Wolf for payment after your job is complete.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_about">
		<text>Stalker, I need someone to who is a bit more experienced than the rookies for a task. Cordon is becoming a very dangerous place with all this rampant mutant breeding going on. I need you to hunt around an area that I will mark on your PDA. The job is to kill any mutants you see. If you do this for me, it will earn you some cash. So will you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Thank you, the rookies will be much safer now because of you. Here is your payment.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- FIND LEVEL 1 TOOLS FOR XENOTECH TASK -->
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Find "%s"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>%s are required by Xenotech to install basic equipment upgrades, you should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>I need a favour, man. A lot of stalkers come by here asking if I can tune their weapons a certain way but I can't. I just don't have the right tools. I would be able to perform upgrades on a greater variety of equipment if I can just get my hands on the right tools. Please, man, will you help me out?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>I need a set of basic tools. It should contain what I need. If you can bring some back for me I will be grateful, I will even offer you a discount from here on out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Okay, yeah, this is exactly what I need. Here, I promised you payment; take it.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- FIND LEVEL 2 TOOLS FOR XENOTECH TASK -->
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Find "%s"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>%s are required by Xenotech to install advanced equipment upgrades, you should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>My business is booming now, more and more stalkers come to me when they need their weapon fine-tuned. But I could really use more tools. You brought me a quality toolkit last time but I need an even higher quality set. If you are interested, I will tell you what I need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>I need an %s. If you can bring one back for me I will be grateful, I will even pay you for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Yes, yes! Here is some cash, you deserve it.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- FIND LEVEL 3 TOOLS FOR XENOTECH TASK -->
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Find "%s"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>%s are required by Xenotech to install expert equipment upgrades, you should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>My business is booming now, more and more stalkers come to me when they need their weapon fine-tuned. But I could really use more tools. You brought me a quality toolkit last time but I need an even higher quality set. If you are interested, I will tell you what I need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>I need an %s. If you can bring one back for me I will be grateful, I will even pay you for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Yes, yes! Here is some cash, you deserve it.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Legend Returns -->
	<!-- Assault the vehicle station for Wolf -->
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_name">
		<text>Eliminate the bandits in the vehicle station</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_text">
		<text>Organize an assault on the vehicle station and destroy the bandits occupying the location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_about">
		<text>The bandits captured the vehicle station again. These bastards rob and kill everyone who uses this road to the village. They frighten off newcomers who hope to find shelter here... Anyway, you must take care of them. Come on! You won't go alone, you'll have two volunteers watching your back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_finish">
		<text>Well done, stalker! Here, right from my heart.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Heart for Sidor -->
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_small_quest_title_0">
		<text>Sidorovich's commission: find the Compass</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_small_quest_text_0">
		<text>Sidorovich asked you to find an artifact - the Compass.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_small_quest_title_1">
		<text>Sidorovich's commission: find the Compass</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_small_quest_text_1">
		<text>Get back to the trader.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_small_quest_title_3">
		<text>Sidorovich's commission: Bring the promised artifact to the trader</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_small_quest_text_3">
		<text>You have found the Compass. You must give it to Sidorovich and demand a fair reward.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- hanter_task -->
	<string id="habarwik_task1_title_0">
		<text>Khabarschik's Legacy: Learn about the seasoned stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="habarwik_task1_text_0">
		<text>In the village lived a stalker who, according to rumors, hid all his bountiful loot somewhere</text>
	</string>
	<string id="habarwik_task1_title_1">
		<text>Legacy of Khabarschik: Find all the stashes of the stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="habarwik_task1_text_1">
		<text>Well, this stalker gave me a serious puzzle! I'll have to sweat a good deal to find all things hidden by him.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Хабарщик -->
	<string id="hanter_task_title_0">
		<text>Destroy the bloodsucker's den</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hanter_task_text_0">
		<text>Hunter asked you to destroy the bloodsucker's lair</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hanter_task_title_1">
		<text>Destroy the bloodsucker's den</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hanter_task_text_1">
		<text>The job's done. You can head back for a reward.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Kill Yoga -->
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_quest1_title_0">
		<text>Sidorovich's Mission: Kill Yoga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_quest1_text_0">
		<text>Sidorovich ordered you to kill the bandit's chieftain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_quest1_title_1">
		<text>Sidorovich's Mission: Kill Yoga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_quest1_text_1">
		<text>The bandit's big cheese is dead. You can head back for a reward.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_quest1_title_3">
		<text>Sidorovich's Mission: Kill Yoga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_quest1_text_3">
		<text>Yoga is in the afterlife, you can now cash in your reward.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
