<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

	<string id="ls_header">
		<text>Legend Returns 0.9.1</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_number">
		<text>Myths and legends from the Zone #</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_1">
		<text>The earth beneath the Zone is honeycombed with passages, rooms and mining shafts. Some stalkers say that there’s a second, even more dreadful underground level under the first one. What is more, there are rumours that even a third level exists which is much more dangerous than the first two…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_2">
		<text>The bloodsucker sneaks up to its prey from behind. It instantly paralyses the victim, then it sucks out the internal organs and blood, leaving precise openings on the body. It can jump from extreme heights without making a sound.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_3">
		<text>Stalkers who have returned from far trips have said that there’s a kindergarten in the dark part of the swamp. Child phantoms were wandering around it, they animated toys and attacked stalkers with them…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_4">
		<text>Someone got to the antennas and got himself irradiated, but that wasn’t the end of it, he began incorporating one correction after another, performed surgery on his inner world. Nobody knows what became of him, his goal was to create a thoroughly developed, godly consciousness for himself, to unlock the subconsciousness and use all resources of his brain…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_5">
		<text>The dark stalkers dress in dark trench coats with a hood firmly pulled over their head so that their face would remain invisible. If you were to throw back the hood, a bald head with red holes for eyes would reveal itself.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_6">
		<text>One of the stalkers who had returned from the Zone said he’d almost reached the Zone’s epicentre where he met an insane old man with a black dog who said that there’s no path for ‘the living’ up ahead. He spoke of the things that await everyone who has managed to get further. Of Pripyat, the Nuclear Power Plant and the underground laboratory which has been here already since 1979.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_7">
		<text>…One way or another, all roads lead to Pripyat. But without disabling at least two emitters, it’s impossible to get there…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_8">
		<text>…Beneath the earth lie the bodies of a common consciousness. Their condition is close to a coma. One of the bodies, controlled underground, is in a laboratory. It fulfills their will, controls inner processes and provides the bodies with all necessities. It is the representative of the ‘C-Consciousness’ project.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_9">
		<text>…It’s the city of zombies and… blind dogs. After each blowout a new wave of ‘zombies’ moves to the city, they flow here from the entire Zone. They ‘live’ in the city as if nothing had happened, scuttle around the streets in a businesslike manner, ‘sleep’ in empty apartments and… certainly don’t love the living.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_10">
		<text>A dark creature is underground where everything has been enveloped by shadows. Stalkers who had descended there were engulfed by darkness, and nobody saw them again.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_11">
		<text>…A bit more and stalkers will make it to the centre of the Zone, and they’ll destroy what they find there. Whether it’s the Black Monolith, an alien ship, or a door into another world, it doesn’t matter. And neither radiation nor cordons, nor anomalies, nor mutants will stop them.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_12">
		<text>What do mutants think about? They think how nice it was when they were living in the warmth and comfort of genetic laboratories. The memories of hurt, abandoned children who take out their resentment and negative emotions on victims.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_13">
		<text>…There are cracks in the walls with some sort of visible glow. If a stalker were to come closer, scores of rats would jump out from the cracks onto his face…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_14">
		<text>‘A monster, that’s what I am,’ the stalker thought. Endless war, the Zone, these artefacts, darned bald patches, what have I turned into? Into a soulless war machine that our generals dreamed of so much? Seems like it. Obviously, I don’t have long left to live. A soldier that ponders over death won’t last long.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_15">
		<text>…They tried to get to the Zone’s centre to do something there and stop, even reverse, the growth and expansion of the Zone’s anomalous areas. It seems that they knew what was really happening in the Zone if they had plans and maps and if they were so hellbent on getting straight to the centre.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_16">
		<text>After the catastrophe and the Zone’s appearance, tales and accounts about strange phenomena near the warehouses began to circulate. The ground nearby glows every now and then, a phosphorescent fog surrounds it, strange droning sounds can be heard and light tremors can be felt.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_17">
		<text>Deep under the ground, at the lowest tunnel level, stalkers have found large metallic gates. Scans have confirmed that there are large underground rooms behind the gates.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_18">
		<text>A group of stalkers believes that the Zone’s centre holds an alien evolutionary module, the ‘Monolith’ crystal. They eradicate stalkers who know too much. They are the last frontier before the power plant.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_19">
		<text>Scientists have developed special medicine which allows people to survive an emission. They have detected strange activity during emissions in the Zone. Now, one of their main tasks is to define the nature of this activity.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_20">
		<text>In the middle of the yellow lake, in the carcass of a building that’s on the remaining part of earth, lies an island with a hole leading underground. There, in darkness, lies the creature in the mist which influences the entire Zone.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_21">
		<text>…They study the Zone and believe that the world is heading towards its end, and before long the Zone’s territory will have increased several times with some countries winding up in it, and their population will not be evacuated in time. They follow and study zombified stalkers and develop new theories on psychotropic weapons and effects.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_22">
		<text>The most valuable thing in the Zone is neither artefacts nor experimental prototypes of new weapons, but rather information and documents which have remained after the catastrophe in abandoned laboratories. With this information one can locate secret warehouses and laboratories, and understand what has happened in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_23">
		<text>A black crystal rests in the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. The stalkers have named it the Monolith. According to a legend which stalkers tell each other, the Monolith fulfills the innermost wishes of the person who has come to it. The most important thing is getting there.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ls_tip_24">
		<text>Stalkers travel around the Zone with their own ambitions which can range from attempts to become rich to investigations why the Zone came to be.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ls_tip_25">
		<text>‘…How long I have been waiting for my time… If I cannot go back to rest, may it come to me!’ The body approaches the stalker with odd jumps, slightly lifting into the air…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_26">
		<text>Military units, led by military stalkers, launched a massive expedition into the Zone. Their aim was to make it to the Zone’s epicentre and eliminate the cause of the appearance of deadly anomalous fields. Practically everyone from the military expedition was completely dead. Isolated groups settled down in the Zone’s territory without any hope of rescue…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_27">
		<text>The ‘Common Consciousness‘ experiment began, and the neuron link of five prisoners gave good results. The ‘C-Consciousness’ possessed slightly less power than the intellect of five human beings. It awoke with rabid neuron activity and its information processing had increased five times. The prisoners’ memory, erased as a precaution, began coming back again…</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_28">
		<text>The blast’s epicentre is one kilometre away from the nuclear power plant. Presumably, the whole staff perished instantly. Many people were caught in the area of effect. Organizing a rescue operation is not considered possible because there are strange energy disturbances in the Zone which present deadly danger for researchers.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_29">
		<text>A few months after the meltdown, a crisis arose: the Zone rapidly grew, swallowing five kilometres of land around it. A large part of the government forces and field laboratories immediately perished. Panic erupted. Inhabitants of villages and cities in the vicinity were hastily evacuated. Danger was looming over the world and its extent could only be surmised.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_30">
		<text>The world was shocked. The Chernobyl of 1986 had returned, bringing a new nightmare with it: the thirty-kilometre Zone, which was swallowing all life forms and leaving only black, oily rot.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_31">
		<text>One of the expeditions found traces of a human staying in the Zone. It was an abandoned camp made by the first stalker. What he did in the Zone and whether he’s alive remains a mystery. Without any devices and relying only on his senses, this man travelled around the Zone while trying to move only at daytime.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ls_tip_32">
		<text>A large group of scientists died while surveying anomalous activity. The group had went approximately three kilometres deep into the Zone when they were caught in a ‘blowout’, a terrible anomalous phenomenon where a human in the open dies in a matter of seconds. A rescue operation was cancelled out of fear, and the dead scientists were considered missing.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ls_tip_33">
		<text>Controllers are former humans with surgical and biochemical changes introduced into their brains. They have the power to control other life forms using microlepton brainwaves (simply put, with telepathy).</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_34">
		 <text>A large military skirmish occurred between a military unit and a returning squad of stalkers. Both sides suffered losses. Hard times were upon stalkers: army units were given permission to shoot on sight at stalkers who were found in the forbidden Zone. There are rumours that soon all exits from the Zone will be blocked off and catching stalkers will begin already in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_35">
		<text>One of the army patrols found an empty dugout which was used to sell artefacts. Nobody knows where they went after getting sold off. The army strengthened its cordons, and patrols flooded the territory next to the Zone. About 70 ‘poaching’ stalkers were caught and approximately 10 underground traders were discovered.</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="ls_tip_36">
		<text>Poachers were becoming more dangerous, not to mention that in army units there were more and more reports of servicemen being bribed and recruited. Increasingly more serious organisations were becoming employers, and stalkers were entering the Zone with gradually better arms and equipment.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_37">
		<text>Everyone is let into the Zone (if you grease some palms), but nobody is let outside. Letting stalkers inside the Zone is profitable for the military because they supposedly contain mutant aggression and haul artefacts to military laboratories for small change.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_38">
		<text>…These objects were called ‘artefacts of the Zone’ and thorough study and acquisition of them began. A year passed, and one day a local old-timer came to a laboratory offering five artefacts for sale, two of which were unknown in type. The laboratory bought all the artefacts, and the old stalker stayed to work for the scientists, bringing more and more new artefacts.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_39">
		<text>The Zone is attracting increasingly more people. One can find not only opportunists from all walks of life, but also scientists, soldiers, and other… ‘patriots’. Various curiosities have appeared in black markets, they are mostly strange and unpredictable. A new profession has appeared for those who live in villages near the Zone: stalking.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_40">
		<text>Two years have passed since the horrible catastrophe occurred and the Zone emerged. During this time radioactive clouds covered much land, an immense amount of dead and missing people, dead animals and burned forests. With it being cordoned off by the military for thirty kilometres, the scientists cannot explain the events.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_41">
		<text>Precautionary measures turned out to be unsatisfactory: the researchers were not prepared for similar events. Upon coming into contact with one of the anaesthetized bodies from the C-Consciousness group, two technicians and a nurse from the support staff were mind-controlled.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_41"> 
	  <text>…The experiment’s leaders reacted immediately and fully isolated the whole block from the outside world. Deadly gas was released through ventilation shafts. 28 mind-controlled humans were beating at their surroundings in convulsions while the ‘C-Consciousness’ was fruitlessly trying to find a way to save itself.</text> 
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_42">
		<text>…The C-Consciousness noticed one-way mirrors through which a group of scientists was observing the experiment. Using telepathy, the group was taken control of and nothing could stop the C-Consciousness anymore. The underground facility’s staff was mind-controlled, and the might of the C-Consciousness multiplied. Approximately 500 people are connected to the C-Consciousness.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_43"> 
	  <text>A number of eyewitness accounts cropped up saying that a strange glow had appeared above the power plant, illuminating the chilly, cloudy and gray morning. After lasting a few hours, the glow disappeared.</text> 
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_44"> 
	 <text>Tenacious rumours have cropped up saying that the sarcophagus is unstable, there are cracks forcing their way through it, no, a blowout is happening… A famous journalist has vanished. Investigation has reached a dead end, and for some reason nobody bothers to take a look at the materials from his journalistic investigations which may conceal the root of all that’s happened… Or maybe they don’t want to? Or they can’t break ties?</text> 
	</string>
	
	<string id="ls_tip_45"> 
	  <text>…And then there’s the general of the Ministry of Internal Affairs who had control over the Chernobyl zone: he ends his own life. It’s mentioned briefly on TV, and then there’s silence again… The means which had been allocated to deal with the last catastrophe are disappearing somewhere without a trace. And once again, it’s swept under the rug. All at once, the media loses interest in this problem…</text> 
	</string>
</string_table>
